<add><doc><field name="title">Immunohistochemical study of marmoset periodontal ligament microvasculature : a confocal laser scanning microscopic study</field><field name="creator">Ashworth, Jonathan F.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 110-120. Reports immunohistochemical investigations into the biological response to the application of an orthodontic force to the buccal segment teeth of marmosets.</field><field name="date">1999</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Marmosets Anatomy</field><field name="subject">Periodontal ligament</field><field name="subject">Immunohistochemistry</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09DM/09dma831.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945251</field></doc><doc><field name="title">H-reflex in human masseter</field><field name="creator">Scutter, Sheila.</field><field name="description">Copies of author's previously published articles inserted. Bibliography: leaves 172-204. H-relexes are used to determine the reflex connections of muscle spindle afferents, the exitability of the motorneuron pool and the integrity of the reflex pathways. However, H-relexes are small and can be difficult to elicit in the masseter, limiting their use in the investigation of the masticatory system. This study investigated the recruitment of masseter motorneurons into the H-reflex, compared to the recruitment occuring during voluntary isometric biting, to determine the distribution of the effective muscle spindle input.</field><field name="date">1999</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Masseter muscle Physiology</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phs4377.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945252</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The influence of insulin-like growth factor 1 and its analogues on fibroblasts and dermal wound healing</field><field name="creator">Marshall, Nicholas John.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliography (leaves 191-219). Examines the levels of insulin-like growth factor and the presence of IGF binding proteins in human wound fluid. Tests the potency of IGF-1 and 2 analogues in in vitro models of fibroblast activity and their effect on healing in normal and diabetic rodent wounds. Shows that IGF-1, IGF-2 and their binding proteins are present in fluid from a partial thickness cutaneous wound; that the binding proteins negatively modulate the activity of insulin-like growth factors in vitro, but that the IGFs do not necessarily show enhanced activity in vivo at the wound site if binding protein affinity is decreased. Discusses possible roles of these binding proteins in wound repair.</field><field name="date">1998</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Somatomedin</field><field name="subject">Wound healing Physiology</field><field name="subject">Wounds and injuries Microbiology</field><field name="subject">Insulin-like growth factor-binding proteins</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09MD/09mdm3685.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945256</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The role of tachykinins in airway inflammation and bronchial hyper-responsiveness</field><field name="creator">Reynolds, Paul N. (Paul Nigel)</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 217-244. Tachykinins are implicated in the mediation of airway inflammatory responses and may have roles in airway remodeling and healing. The actions of tachykinins are mediated by specific receptors, designated NK1, NK2 and NK3. Tachykinin degredation, an important mechanism for limiting the effects of these peptides, is principally mediated by neutral endopeptidase (NEP). This thesis investigates the role of tachykinins, in vivo, in an ovine model and in human airway epithelium. Results show that the nett effect of tachykinins in the airway will depend on the relative balance between the expression of receptors, tachykinins and NEP. Assessment of these molecules in the airway epithelium from subjects with normal lungs or chronic bronchitis showed that preprotachykinin-A gene expression was relatively higher in the disease group whereas NEP and NK1 receptor levels were unchanged. These studies provide new insights into the role of tachykinins in airways disease.</field><field name="date">1999</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Tachykinins</field><field name="subject">Respiratory organs Diseases</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phr464.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945261</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Resting forearm blood-tissue lactate and gas exchange kinetics during supine leg exercise</field><field name="creator">Catcheside, Peter.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 230-255. The work described in this thesis was stimulated by the observation that during leg exercise, resting forearm lactate kinetics appear to resemble closely the blood-tissue exchange kinetics of inert gases that have been reported in many organs during inert gas inhalation. Two mathematical models of forearm lactate uptake were developed, and three series of experiments were conducted to investigate the contribution and impact of passive (inert-like) lactate movements to veno-arterial concentration differences in the resting forearm during leg exercise. The results are discussed.</field><field name="date">1999</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Lactates</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phc357.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945265</field></doc><doc><field name="title">A comparative study of male germ cell production in two Australian conilurine rodents, the plains rat, Pseudomys australis and hopping mouse, Notomys alexis</field><field name="creator">Peirce, Eleanor J.</field><field name="description">Copies of author's previously published articles inserted. Bibliography: p. 199-254. In eutherian mammals, the size of the testes and number of spermatozoa produced and stored in the excurrent ducts vary widely between species, with the hydromyine rodents of Australia exhibiting a greater range of interspecific variation than any other closely related group of species. This study compared the efficiency of germ cell production and sperm storage capacity in the extra-testicular ducts of two arid zone species, the plains rat, Pseudomys australis, and the spinifex hopping mouse, Notomys alexis, that have vast differences in testes size and number of stored spermatozoa. Results are discussed.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Pseudomys australis Anatomy</field><field name="subject">Notomys alexis Anatomy</field><field name="subject">Germ cells</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09php378.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945266</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The Influence of the CYP2C19 and CYP2D6 genetic polymorphisms on oxidative drug metabolism</field><field name="creator">Coller, Janet K.</field><field name="description">Amendements: leaves 252-254. Copies of author's previously published articles inserted. Bibliography: leaves 226-251. The CYP2C19 and CYP2D6 genetic polymorphisms control the oxidative metabolism of many different drug classes. Populations are separated into groups of extensive metabolisers (EM), poor metabolisers (PM), and in the case of CYP2D6, ultra-rapid metabolisers (UM). In vitro studies using human liver microsomes were conducted to examine the kinetics of the oxidative metabolism of flunitrazepam, and which CYP450 enzymes mediate the oxidative metabolism of flunitrazepam, (S)-mephenytoin and proguanil.</field><field name="date">1999</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Drugs Metabolism</field><field name="subject">Genetic polymorphisms</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phc6968.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945267</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Language usage and language attitudes among education consumers : the experience of Filipinos in Australia and in three linguistic communities in the Philippines</field><field name="creator">Nical, Iluminado C.</field><field name="description">Errata inserted facing t. p. Bibliography: leaves 406-457. A comparative investigation of language usage and language attitudes in relation to Filipino/Tagalog, Philippine languages other than Tagalog and English among senior high school students and their parents in two countries, the Philippines and Australia. The study provides an historical overview of the development of national language policies in Australia and in the Philippines, focussing on the way in which multiculturalism in Australia influenced language policies, and on the reasons for the adoption of the Bilingual Education Program in the Philippines.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Language and languages Cross-cultural studies</field><field name="subject">Philippines Languages</field><field name="subject">Australia Languages</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phn582.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945268</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Relationships between motor and sensory function in the proximal gut, appetite, &amp; nutrients in healthy human subjects</field><field name="creator">Andrews, Jane Mary.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 206-251. The motor and sensory interactions between nutrients and proximal gut in humans are not well understood, despite the pivotal importance of these interactions on appetite, absorption and thus, nutrition. In part, this lack of knowledge results from technical difficulties in studying motor function in the human gut. In particular, the inability to continuously measure intraluminal flow with any degree of temporal resolution, has impeded progress in this field. The studies described in this thesis focus on nutrient-gut interactions, and also on the development of novel methodologies aimed at advancing the understanding and interpretation of the relationships between intraluminal pressures and flows.</field><field name="date">1999</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Gastrointestinal system Motility</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09pha567.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945295</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Regulation of food intake, body fat stores and energy balance in the marsupial Sminthopsis crassicaudata</field><field name="creator">Hope, Perdita Jane.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 363-421. This thesis presents studies relating to the regulation of appetite, body fat stores and energy balance in the marsupial Sminthopsis crassicaudata. All of the studies presented have been published in international journals, accepted for publication, or submitted for publication. These studies have provided novel data on the regulation of food intake, body fat stores and energy balance in the marsupail Sminthopsis crassicaudata, representing fundamental advances in marsupial biology.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Sminthopsis crassicaudata</field><field name="subject">Bioenergetics</field><field name="subject">Marsupials Nutrition</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phh7908.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945296</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Physicochemical properties of protein inclusion bodies</field><field name="creator">Wangsa-Wirawan, Norbertus Djajasantosa.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 182-198. Improvements in the current production system of inclusion bodies and the downstream processing sequence are essential to maintain a competitive advantage in the market place. Optimisation of fermentation is considered to improve production yield; then flotation as a possible inclusion body recovery method.</field><field name="date">1999</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Escherichia coli Inclusions</field><field name="subject">Recombinant proteins Analysis</field><field name="subject">Particle size distribution</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phw2465.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945297</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Functional characterisation of the ubiquitin-protein ligase, Nedd4</field><field name="creator">Harvey, Kieran F.</field><field name="description">Addenda pasted into back end-paper. Bibliography: leaves 107-147. The studies presented in this thesis have identified Nedd4 as a key protein involved in Na+-dependent downregulation of the epithelial Na+ channel (ENaC). These studies have aided in the molecular understanding of the familial hypertensive disorder, Liddle's syndrome, and the regulation of blood pressure in general.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phh3411.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945298</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Studies on the growth and metabolism of Eikenella corrodens / Neville Gully</field><field name="creator">Gully, Neville.</field><field name="description">Copies of author's previously published articles inserted. Bibliography: leaves 175-194. Eikenella corrodens, a Gram-negative rod, is a normal inhabitant of the human oral cavity. It is one of the most commonly detected cultivable bacteria from sub- and supra-gingival plaque and is often isolated in elevated proportions from sites exhibiting destructive periodontal disease compared with healthy sites. The primary aim of this study was to investigate the metabolism of  E. corrodons, with particular reference to energy generation, and to determine the effect of physical environmental parameters on its growth.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Periodontal disease Microbiology</field><field name="subject">Periodontal disease Molecular aspects</field><field name="subject">Microbial metabolism</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phg973.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945322</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Tumour metastasis and dissemination during laparoscopic surgery</field><field name="creator">Neuhaus, Susan J.</field><field name="description">Copies of author's previously published articles enclosed. Bibliography: leaves 217-258. Examines recent literature which describes cases of metastatic involvement of laparoscopic port sites, not only in patients with advanced tumors but in patients with early stage carcinoma, and even in patients following laparoscopic procedures during which tumors were not disturbed. This thesis utilises an established small animal model to investigate the aetiology of port site metasrases and the efficacy of preventative strategies in reducing tumor implantation following laparoscopy.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Laparoscopic surgery Complications</field><field name="subject">Metastasis</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phn485.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945323</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Performance improvement through predicated execution in VLIW machines</field><field name="creator">Biglari-Abhari, Morteza.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 136-153. Investigates techniques to achieve performance improvement in Very Long Instruction Word machines through predicated execution.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Compilers (Computer programs)</field><field name="subject">Computer architecture</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phb593.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945324</field></doc><doc><field name="title">A study of the molecular and biological characteristics of ovine interleukin-12</field><field name="creator">Swinburne, Sarah Jane.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 172-214. Interleukin-12 (IL-12) is a heterodimeric cytokine composed of two disulphide-linked subunits, p35 and p40, which form biologically active p70. IL-12 is able to induce IFN-y production from T and NK cells, and promote the proliferation of mitogen-activated T cells. It is thought that IL-12 may be an important cytokine in the initiation and progression of allograft destruction. This thesis describes the characterisation of ovine IL-12.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Interleukin-12</field><field name="subject">Sheep Physiology</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phs9777.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945325</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Acute drug effects on the heart-haemodynamic, pharmacologic and metabolic correlations</field><field name="creator">Zeitz, Christopher John.</field><field name="description">Addenda and corrigenda inserted on verso of back end paper. Includes: Publications and communications to learned societies (p. 4-5). Bibliography: leaves 272-286. Examines the acute myocardial uptake of drugs, particularly perindoprilat and enalaprilat in humans. The uptake of these agents is examined, together with the haemodynamic, metabolic and biochemical effects. In particular, the impact of these agents on angiotensin and bradykinin peptides both within the heart and peripherally is described. The acute effects of a range of cardioactive drugs upon the left ventricular force-interval relationship is examined.</field><field name="date">1999</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Heart Effect of drugs on</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phz48.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945326</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Oxygen toxicity and radiation injury to the pulmonary system</field><field name="creator">McLennan, Geoffrey.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 168-184. The work in this study encompasses oxygen free radical related inflammation in the peripheral lung and in lung cells. Animal and human studies have been used. Methods include cell culture with function studies, protein chemistry, animal and human physiology, and cell and lung structure through histopathology, and various forms of electron microscopy. The work resulting from this thesis has formed an important basis for understanding acute and chronic lung injury.</field><field name="date">1997</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Lungs Pathophysiology</field><field name="subject">Lungs Inflammation</field><field name="subject">Lungs Radiation injuries</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phm164.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945327</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Molecular analysis of Legionella longbeachae serogroup 1 virulence</field><field name="creator">Doyle, Robyn Michelle.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 246-304. Describes experiments aimed at characterising the potential virilant factors of Legionella longbeachae sg 1, an important human pathogen which is responsible for nearly half of all clinical cases of Legionella related pneumonia reported each year.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Legionella longbeachae</field><field name="subject">Legionnaires' disease</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phd7546.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945328</field></doc><doc><field name="title">French and T&#226;y B&#7891;i in Vietnam : a study of language policy, practice and perceptions</field><field name="creator">Love, Susan.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: p. 219-229. This thesis examines the policy and practice of French language use in Vietnam, with particular reference to T&#226;y B&#7891;i, a pidgin French spoken during the colonial era.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">French language Vietnam</field><field name="subject">Pidgin languages Vietnam</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09ARM/09arml897.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945330</field></doc><doc><field name="title">An investigation of the educational outcomes of participation in a study skills program for a group of adult secondary students</field><field name="creator">Aylen, Beryl J.</field><field name="description">Addendum fixed inside back end-paper. Bibliography: leaves 216-219. Reports a study to investigate the influence of a study skills program on a group of adult students at Thebarton Senior College, Adelaide. The researcher planned and prepared the program of work for these students and was the teacher of the subject, and the observer of the influence the course had on the students, compared with a similar control group. Analysis showed there was an observable positive effect on the students, however, it was the conclusion of the researcher that the positive result was achieved more because support had been offered to the students than through the teaching of the subject matter of the study skills course.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Adult education South Australia</field><field name="subject">Study skills South Australia</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09EDM/09edma978.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945332</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Green tea and its catechins modulate cholesterol metabolism in cultured human liver (HepG2) cells and the hypercholesterolaemic rabbit</field><field name="creator">Bursill, Christina.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (21 leaves). Previous studies have found that green tea and its antitoxidant constituents, the catechins, are hypocholesterolaemic in both epidemiological and animal intervetion studies. The main objectives of the present study were to investigate the mechanism by which green tea and its most abundant catechin constituent epigallocatechin gallate increase the low-density lipoprotein (LDL) receptor of HepG2 cells. In addition, it was hoped to determine if a crude catechin extract from green tea could lower plasma cholesterol levels in the hypercholesterolaemic rabbit and ascertain if this effect was due to an increase in the LDL receptor. The study provides evidence that green tea and its catechins exhibit hypocholesterolaemic properties and may therefore provide protection against heart disease.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Heart Diseases Prevention</field><field name="subject">Anticholesteremic agents</field><field name="subject">Green tea</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09pdb9725.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945340</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Development in the Port Jackson shark embryo</field><field name="creator">Rodda, Kate R. (Kate Rose)</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 202-238. Gives an overall understanding of embryonic development of Heterodontus portusjacksoni.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Sharks Australia Embryology</field><field name="subject">Sharks Physiology</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phr686.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945349</field></doc><doc><field name="title">MF radar observations of tides and planetary waves</field><field name="creator">Kovalam, Sujata.</field><field name="description">Copies of previously published articles inserted. Bibliography: p. 185-200. Data obtained from six radar stations covering a wide latitude range has been used to determine the global distribution of planetary waves and tides. In the process a number of data analyses techniques were considered for their characterisation.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Atmospheric tides</field><field name="subject">Rossby waves</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phk878.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945350</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Transient phase conjugation using Stimulated Brillouin Scattering</field><field name="creator">Afshaarvahid, Shahraam.</field><field name="description">Copies of author's previously published articles inserted. Bibliography: p. 169-176. Develops a one and three dimensional transient model of Stimulated Brillouin Scattering to investigate the transient regime of Stimulated Brillouin Scattering and recognize different transient phenomena that affect its performance.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Brillouin scattering</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09pha2583.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945351</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The response to environmental economic drivers by civil engineering contractors in South Australia</field><field name="creator">Burroughs, Gary Leslie.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 91-93. Examines the response of two civil engineering construction contractors in South Australia to environmental economic conditions and market requirements using primarily an action research methodology whilst the researcher was engaged as the environmental manager at both corporations.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Construction industry South Australia Management</field><field name="subject">Construction industry South Australia Environmental aspects</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09ENV/09envb972.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945353</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Urban stormwater management in Vietnam</field><field name="creator">Le Phu Vo.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 84-91. Examines the current status of urban stormwater and water resources management in Vietnam</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Urban runoff Vietnam Management</field><field name="subject">Storm sewers Vietnam</field><field name="subject">Water quality management Vietnam</field><field name="subject">Water Pollution Vietnam</field><field name="subject">Sewage disposal Vietnam Management</field><field name="subject">Sewage Environmental aspects Vietnam</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09ENV/09envl595.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945354</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Assessing the environmental performance of building developments : the Green Building Tool</field><field name="creator">Sheppard, Barbara Dorothea.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: p. 119-122. Aims to show how the GB Tool (Green BuildingTool) can be used to access the environmental performance of residential building developments, with a focus on South Australia. Describes the history of, and rationale for, the GB Tool; and its practical implementation. Identifies some theoretical short comings of the GB Tool, as well as some practical difficulties with using it.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Buildings Environmental engineering</field><field name="subject">Architecture and energy conservation South Australia</field><field name="subject">Building materials Environmental aspects South Australia</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09ENV/09envs549.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945355</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Mindscapes and landscapes : an ontological analysis of aesthetic relationships between visual arts and nature</field><field name="creator">O'Hara, Maeve.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 99-102. Identifies aesthetic knowledge as a fundamentally linked perceptual and ontological process. Aesthetic processes are identified as criteria relevant for locating and advocating ethics in 'eco-culturally sustainable development'. Cultural actions are ethical evaluations about valuing nature.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Environmental ethics</field><field name="subject">Social ecology</field><field name="subject">Aesthetics, Modern</field><field name="subject">Conservation of natural resources</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09ENV/09envo36.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945356</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The Fiji sugar industry in the context of sustainable development : lessons from a local survey</field><field name="creator">Nair, Veena D. (Veena Devi)</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 92-98. Considers the issue of achieving sustainable development in a society operating under the constraints of poverty, lack of environmental awareness and political instability.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Sugar trade Fiji Environmental aspects</field><field name="subject">Economic development Environmental aspects Fiji</field><field name="subject">Social responsibility of business</field><field name="subject">Sustainable development</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09ENV/09envn158.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945357</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Cleaner production : promoting and achieving it in the South Australian foundry industry</field><field name="creator">Larwood, Andrew John.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 123-130. The literature search and the findings from the investigation have been used to provide recommendations for a sector specific cooperative approach using regulation, self-regulation, voluntary agreements, economic incentatives and educational/information strategies to promote and acheive cleaner production in the South Australian foundry industry.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Industrial management Environmental aspects South Australia</field><field name="subject">Environmental protection South Australia</field><field name="subject">Factory and trade waste Environmental aspects South Australia</field><field name="subject">Foundries South Australia Environmental aspects</field><field name="subject">Social responsibility of business South Australia</field><field name="subject">Waste minimization South Australia</field><field name="subject">Environmental engineering</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09ENV/09envl336.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945358</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The diffusion of HIV/AIDS in sub Saharan Africa : the role of social, economic and cultural factors</field><field name="creator">Lukong, Paul Forka.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 103-113. Uses GIS to map the pattern of widespread transmission, commercial sex workers, poverty prevalence, illiteracy rate, population displacement and other social indicators to show the vulnerability of the region's population; and to demonstrate that there is no single point of radiation of HIV/AIDS in the sub region. Discusses mitigation and prevention strategies and proposes the use of GIS be incorporated in the fight against HIV/AIDS in sub Saharan Africa.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Sexually transmitted diseases Social aspects Africa, Sub-Saharan Remote sensing</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09ENV/09envl954.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945359</field></doc><doc><field name="title">High power scalable diode-laser-pumped CW Nd:YAG laser using a stable-unstable resonator</field><field name="creator">Mudge, Damien.</field><field name="description">Copies of author's previously published articles, inserted. Bibliography: p. 165-179. Reports on the development of a scalable high power laser for gravitational wave interferometry.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Interferometry</field><field name="subject">Wave mechanics</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phm9438.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945363</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Mid-Palaeozoic shear zones in the Strangways Range : a record of intracratonic tectonism in the Arunta Inlier, Central Australia</field><field name="creator">Bendall, Betina.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: p.127-141.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Geology, Stratigraphic Proterozoic</field><field name="subject">Orogeny Northern Territory Arunta Block</field><field name="subject">Geology, Structural Northern Territory Arunta Block</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phb458.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945371</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Ionospheric scintillation effects on global positioning system receivers</field><field name="creator">Knight, Mark Frederick.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: p. 297-304. Uses a widely accepted stochastic model of scintillation activity to investigate the effects of scintillations on GPS receivers and systems.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Global Positioning System</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phk698.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:22945372</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Hydrodynamic stability of boundary-layer flows in the presence of mass transfer</field><field name="creator">Halatchev, Iordan Atanassov.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 201-207. This thesis presents studies of the non-linear mass-transfer kinetics and a linear analysis of the hydrodynamic stability of systems under conditions of intense interfacial mass transfer.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Boundary layer</field><field name="subject">Dynamics</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phh157.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23137210</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Systematic relationships within the Litsea complex (Lauraceae)</field><field name="creator">Li, Jie.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 242-252) A general description of the taxonomic history, embryology, palynology, karyology, anatomy and distribution of the Litsea complex and providing an improved classification for the complex and a key to the revised genera. System requirements for accompanying computer disk: IBM compatible computer. Other requirements: LucID Software.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Lauraceae</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phl6927.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23137212</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Sugarcane striate mosaic associated virus : RNA sequence and genome organisation, taxonomy and detection</field><field name="creator">Thompson, Nicole, 1975-</field><field name="description">Includes corrigendum attached to back leaf. Bibliography: leaves 114-132. This thesis describes the complete nucleotide sequence and genome organisation of SCSMaV-RNA, examines the taxonomy of SCSMaV by phylogenetic analysis, and describes the development of diagnostic tests for application to field study. (abstract)</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Sugarcane mosaic virus Genetics</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09pht4744.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23137268</field></doc><doc><field name="title">In the shadows of consciousness : uncanny composures in the City of Adelaide</field><field name="creator">Weir, Michael John, 1955-</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 381-418. Examines the actions of ordinary people within a city landscape with the major focus on the politics of meaning and culture in cities . Case studies are drawn from Adelaide.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Sociology, Urban</field><field name="subject">Anthropology Philosophy</field><field name="subject">Geographical perception</field><field name="subject">Space (Architecture)</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phw425.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23137278</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Chronic pain in older people</field><field name="creator">Kung, Francis Tat-yan.</field><field name="description">Typescript (photocopy) Includes bibliographical references (leaves: 260-304)</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">VU</field><field name="subject">Pain in old age</field><field name="subject">Chronic pain Patients</field><field name="subject">Older people Medical care</field><field name="subject">Older people Health aspects</field><field name="identifier">http://adt1.lib.unimelb.edu.au/adt-root/public/adt-VU2001.0028/index.html</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23140540</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Initial frequencies of alleles for resistance to Bacillus thuringiensis toxins in field populations of Plutella xylostella and Helicoverpa armigera</field><field name="creator">Ahmad, Mahmood.</field><field name="description">Leaves 101-104 are misnumbered. Bibliography: leaves 155-215. In this study thirteen populations of P. xylostella from crucifer growing areas of Queensland, Victoria, Tasmania, South Australia and Western Australia were surveyed for resistance to Bt (Bacillus thuringiensis)  toxins using a leaf-dip bioassay method.</field><field name="date">1999</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Pests Biological control</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09pha2851.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23206960</field></doc><doc><field name="title">White noise analysis and stochastic evolution equations</field><field name="creator">Sorensen, Julian Karl.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 127-128.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Stochastic analysis</field><field name="subject">Hilbert spaces</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phs713.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23206970</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Breast cancer screening and medical negligence : 'waiting for something to happen'</field><field name="creator">Chapple, Bronwyn.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 48-50.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09MPM/09mpmc467.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23206982</field></doc><doc><field name="title">General practitioner willingness to conduct follow-up care of patients with colorectal cancer</field><field name="creator">McGorm, Kelly Jane.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 78-85.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09MPM/09mpmm146.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23206984</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The elderly in Vietnam today and tomorrow : economic, cultural and political perspectives</field><field name="creator">Le, Huyen Thi Thanh.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 93-99.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09MPM/09mpml433.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23206988</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The role of vesicular-arbuscular mycorrhizal fungi in Linum usitatissimum L. production in Southern Australian soils</field><field name="creator">Thomas, Benjamin Mark.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 106-132. This project investigated the role of VAM fungi in the growth and nutrition of Linum usitatissimum L. in agricultural soils in southern Australia. It had two general aims: (1) to examine the role of indigenous VAM fungi in the growth and nutrition of linseed in field soil collected near Clare, South Australia; and (2) to examine the effect of VAM fungi on the Zn nutrition of Linola.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Flax</field><field name="subject">Crops and soils South Australia</field><field name="subject">Mycorrhizal fungi</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09pht4541.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23207031</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The history of the Torrens system of land registration with special reference to its German origins</field><field name="creator">Esposito, Antonio Kurt.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references. The origins of the Torrens System of land registration are not clear. Examines the claim of Dr. Ulrich H&#252;bbe who asserted that he collaborated with Torrens to bring about the adoption of the land law of his hometown Hamburg in the form of the Real Property Act 1858 (SA). An historical examination (collecting and analysing all relevant historical sources), shows that it is likely that H&#252;bbe was the actual draftsman, while a comparative legal analysis (contrasting Hamburg's land law at the beginning of the 19th century with the first bill of the Act) demonstrates that there is a strong similarity between Hamburg's land registration system and the original Torrens System; and, that the outstanding differences between the systems can be explained by the natural adaptation processes which are implied by the adoption of laws.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">H&#252;bbe, Ulrich</field><field name="subject">Torrens, Robert, Sir, 1814-1884</field><field name="subject">South Australia. Real Property Act 1858</field><field name="subject">Torrens system South Australia</field><field name="subject">Land titles Registration and transfer South Australia</field><field name="subject">Real property South Australia</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09LM/09lme77.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23218467</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Factors influencing student outcomes in university agricultural courses : building and testing explanatory models</field><field name="creator">Quinn, Petrina.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: v.1 leaves 291-318 Electronic version requires Adobe Acrobat</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">NCSU:W</field><field name="subject">Charles Sturt University Dissertations</field><field name="subject">Academic achievement Australia</field><field name="subject">College students Australia Attitudes</field><field name="identifier">http://www.csu.edu.au/division/library/ereserve/thesesbyauthor.htm</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23442425</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Modelling long-term persistence in hydrological time series</field><field name="creator">Thyer, Mark Andrew.</field><field name="description">Department of Civil, Surveying and Environmental Engineering. Includes bibliographical references (leaves R-1--R-9)</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">NNCU:A</field><field name="subject">Time-series analysis</field><field name="subject">Hydrology Mathematical models</field><field name="identifier">http://www.newcastle.edu.au/services/library/adt/public/adt-NNCU20020531.035349/index.html</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23500032</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Environmental factors in child behaviours in an early childhood setting</field><field name="creator">Baxter, Roger A.</field><field name="description">Faculty of Education. Includes bibliographical references (leaves 243-286)</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">NNCU:A</field><field name="subject">Behavioral assessment of children</field><field name="subject">Day care centers</field><field name="subject">Behavior disorders in children</field><field name="subject">Day care centers Activity programs</field><field name="subject">Social interaction in children</field><field name="identifier">http://www.newcastle.edu.au/services/library/adt/public/adt-NNCU20030228.094947/index.html</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23502057</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Gender dynamics in an engineering classroom engineering students' perspectives</field><field name="creator">Burrowes, Gunilla.</field><field name="description">Faculty of Engineering. Includes bibliographical references (leaves 133-141)</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">NNCU:A</field><field name="subject">Sex differences in education Australia</field><field name="subject">Engineering Study and teaching (Higher) Sex differences</field><field name="subject">Women in engineering Australia</field><field name="identifier">http://www.newcastle.edu.au/services/library/adt/public/adt-NNCU20021210.142001</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23502083</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Disinfection by-products in drinking water and genotoxic changes in urinary bladder epithelial cells</field><field name="creator">Ranmuthugala, Geethanjali Piyawadani.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 263-270.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">ANU</field><field name="subject">Disinfection and disinfectants Carcinogenicity</field><field name="subject">Epidemiology Research Australia</field><field name="subject">Trihalomethanes Health aspects</field><field name="subject">Water Purification Disinfection By-products</field><field name="identifier">http://thesis.anu.edu.au/public/adt-ANU20011207.110344/index.html</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23531232</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Causes, consequences and challenges of rural-urban migration in Bangladesh</field><field name="creator">Afsar, Rita.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 331-404) Attempts to contribute toward greater understanding of the urbanization process in Bangladesh. Focuses particularly on the rural-urban migration process, explaining the causes of mobility and stability and the consequences flowing from that movement for the wellbeing of migrants and their families.</field><field name="date">1995</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Rural-urban migration Bangladesh Dhaka</field><field name="subject">Urbanization Bangladesh Dhaka</field><field name="subject">Squatters Bangladesh Dhaka</field><field name="subject">Dhaka (Bangladesh) Social conditions</field><field name="subject">Dhaka (Bangladesh) Economic conditions</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09pha258.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23673565</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Ecological and molecular studies on rhizobial rhizopines</field><field name="creator">Heinrich, Keith.</field><field name="description">Corrigendum attached to back cover. Includes bibliographical references (leaves 160-190). Investigates the role of rhizopines in rhizobial  competition for nodulation, and to isolate the rhizopine synthesis genes in Rhizobium leguminosarum bv. viciae.</field><field name="date">1999</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Rhizobium leguminosarum Molecular aspects</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phh469.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23674284</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Speaking the unspeakable : war trauma in six contemporary novels</field><field name="creator">Mackinnon, Jeremy E.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 246-258) Presents readings of six novels which depict something of the nature of war trauma. Collectively, the novels suggest that the attempt to narrativise war trauma is inherently problematic. Traces the disjunctions between narrative and war trauma which ensure that war trauma remains an elusive and private phenomonen; the gulf between private experience and public discourse haunts each of the novels.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Psychic trauma in literature</field><field name="subject">War Psychological aspects Fiction</field><field name="subject">Psychoanalysis and literature</field><field name="subject">Psychology in literature</field><field name="subject">American literature History and criticism Theory, etc</field><field name="subject">English fiction History and criticism Theory, etc</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phm15821.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23674595</field></doc><doc><field name="title">An electrophysiological investigation of colonic afferent sensitivity in the rat and mouse - in vitro</field><field name="creator">Lynn, Penelope Ann.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 136-156) Two novel in vitro preparations were developed from which recordings were made from colonic afferents in the rat and mouse.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Afferent pathways</field><field name="subject">Colon (Anatomy) Innervation</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phl989.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23674596</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Wear studies of enamel and some restorative materials</field><field name="creator">Shabanian-Borojeni, Mitra.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves [1-20]). A systematic analysis of wear involving the in vitro analysis of the wear of standard composite resin and glass ionomer cements restorations under controlled conditions; and, the qualitative and quantitative investigation of wear over a range of pH's and loads which might be encountered clinically in order to develop a "wear map" of the micromorphology of wearing teeth and restorations and a systematic modeling of wear rates.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Dental materials Evaluation</field><field name="subject">Dental enamel Deterioration</field><field name="subject">Teeth Abrasion</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phs5241.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23674597</field></doc><doc><field name="title">What matter who's speaking : Samuel Beckett and the author-function</field><field name="creator">Smith, Russell, 1968-</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 309-330) Resists the notion of a subversive Beckett appropriated by the cultural mainstream, by tracing the discursive limits of avante-garde writing, and by exploring how Beckett paradoxically reinforced the traditional author-function even as he appeared to challenge it.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Beckett, Samuel, 1906- Criticism and interpretation</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phs658.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23674599</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Leukocyte elastase and anti-elastases in pulmonary emphysema</field><field name="creator">Walsh, Robert Leo.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 218-249) The preferred theory to explain the aetiology of emphysema points to an imbalance in the protease-antiprotease systems within the lung with human leukocyte elastase and [alpha]1-protease inhibiter being the main candidates. Examines some aspects of this theory.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Emphysema, Pulmonary Pathophysiology</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phw2261.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23674600</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Economically beneficial drug interactions with cyclosporin and tacroliumus : clinical studies in recipients of kidney and liver transplants</field><field name="creator">Jones, Terence Edward.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 234-257. Three separate clinical studies in organ transplant recipients are presented. The aims are to examine fundamental questions regarding the clinically and economically important pharmokinetic interaction between diltiazem and cyclosporin, an interaction widely utilised in organ transplantation. The data contained should assist the development of soundly based policies that will ensure a benefit exists before a sparing agent is coprescribed, and that the lowest effective dose of sparing agent is used.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">FK-506 (Drug)</field><field name="subject">Cyclosorine</field><field name="subject">Immunosuppressive agents Mechanism of action</field><field name="subject">Immunosuppressive agents Economic aspects</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phj79.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23674671</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Schooling quality and economic growth</field><field name="creator">Neri, Frank.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 148-155. This thesis investigates whether cross-country variations in schooling quality (the productivity of the time spent studying) affect the empirical results in studies of economic growth based on an augmented method of Solow. It was found that schooling quality is positively and statistically significantly associated with mean economic growth rates in regressions which control for physical capital investment rates, population growth rates and secondary school enrolment rates. Education levels of parents, hours of homework and the non-teaching duties of teachers were also significant determinants.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Economic development Effect of education on</field><field name="subject">Education Economic aspects</field><field name="subject">Human capital</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phn445.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23674672</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The effects of estrogens and phytoestrogens on the metabolism and oxidation of plasma lipoproteins</field><field name="creator">Owen, Alice, 1972-</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 172-217). Examines the effects of estrogens and phytoestrogens on plasma lipoprotein levels and other risk factors for cardiovascular disease, including the oxidisability of low density lipoprotein</field><field name="date">1999</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Blood lipoproteins Metabolism</field><field name="subject">Blood lipoproteins Oxidation</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09pho968.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23674673</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Mechanisms of intracellular and extracellular cytokine production from the human leukaemia inhibitory factor gene</field><field name="creator">Voyle, Roger Bruce.</field><field name="description">Addendum attached to back facing leaves. Includes bibliographical references (leaves 172-199). The findings establish leukemia inhibitory factor, and possibly oncostatin M, as new members of a small but growing class of cytokines produced in an intracellularly active form and also suggest that the production of alternate transcripts and intercellularly-retained proteins may be a common and important feature of cytokines of the IL-6 and other families.</field><field name="date">1999</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Leukemia inhibitory factor</field><field name="subject">Interleukin-6</field><field name="subject">Leukemia Physiopathology</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phv975.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23674674</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Identification and management of somatization in the primary care setting, in terms of illness behaviour and risk of psychiatric illness</field><field name="creator">Scicchitano, Janice Patricia.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 233-306. A study of the phenomenon of somatization as it occurs in the primary care setting. The phenomenon was studied in terms of aspects of illness behaviour and risk of psychiatric morbidity. It is suggested that abnormal illness behaviour in the form of somatization may be an important factor in the non-recognition of mild non-psychotic psychiatric illness in the primary care setting. The results of the study indicate that an assessment of the patients' attitudes and beliefs about symptoms, and an exploration of psychosocial issues, may lead to a better understanding of why the patients have sought help, and may lead to early identification and appropriate treatment of somatizing behaviour and the psychiatric morbidity underlying such behaviour.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Somatization disorder</field><field name="subject">Family medicine</field><field name="subject">Primary care (Medicine)</field><field name="subject">Mental illness Diagnosis</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phs416.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23674675</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Studies in paediatric urology</field><field name="creator">Dewan, P. A. (Patrick Arthur)</field><field name="description">Includes list of publications and presentations by the author. Bibliography: leaves 166-194. A collection of laboratory and clinical studies in paediatric urology, including prospective and retrospective patient series, case reports of rare conditions. Also, technical innovations are documented and reviewed in light of international experience.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Pediatric urology</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09MSM/09msmd515.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23674682</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The impact of migration upon family structure and functioning in Java</field><field name="creator">Wahyuni, Ekawati Sri.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 444-460). A study based on a case study with integrated macro and micro approaches to investigate some effects of the development and industrialisation processes in Indonesia.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Family Indonesia Java Social conditions 20th</field><field name="subject">Family demography Indonesia Java</field><field name="subject">Migration, Internal Indonesia Java</field><field name="subject">Industrialization Indonesia Java Case studies</field><field name="subject">Indonesia Economic conditions 1997-</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phw1368.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23674690</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Investigation of the 'anorexia of ageing'</field><field name="creator">MacIntosh, Caroline Gabrielle.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 349-421) Addresses some of the mechanisms which may potentially contribute to the physiological anorexia of ageing, as suggested by previous animal and human studies.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Nutrition Social aspects</field><field name="subject">Age factors in disease</field><field name="subject">Older people Diseases Prevention</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phm15187.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23674694</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Optical studies of the mesospheric region</field><field name="creator">Woithe, Jonathan Mark.</field><field name="description">Includes copies of articles co-authored by the author during the preparation of this thesis. Includes bibliographical references (leaves 233-245). A three-field photometer was employed at the University of Adelaide's Buckland Park field site to collect optical observations of the 557.7nm OI and 730nm OH airglow emissions on an almost continuous basis since May 1995 to May 2000, with observations made whenever the moon was not up.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Airglow Observations</field><field name="subject">Gravity waves</field><field name="subject">Mesosphere</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phw847.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23674696</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The identification and characterisation of two novel Drosophila caspases, DRONC and DECAY</field><field name="creator">Dorstyn, Loretta Esterina.</field><field name="description">Includes a list of publications co-authored by the author during the preparation of this thesis. Thesis amendments in back leaf. Includes bibliographical references (leaves 123-168). The studies described concentrate on the cloning and characterisation of the two Drosophila caspases, DRONC and DECAY</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Drosophila Molecular genetics</field><field name="subject">Apoptosis Immunological aspects</field><field name="subject">Cell death</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phd718.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23674697</field></doc><doc><field name="title">A study of bibracchial lariat ether complexes and linked cyclodextrin dimer complexes</field><field name="creator">West, Lee Charles.</field><field name="description">Includes errata attached to first leaf. Includes bibliographical references. The complexation of a range of monovalent and divalent metal ions by the bibracchial lariat ethers has been investigated. Also investigates the complexation of metal ions and the anionic azo dye Brilliant Yellow by the diazacrown linked cyclodextrin dimers.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Cyclodextrins</field><field name="subject">Azo compounds</field><field name="subject">Clathrate compounds</field><field name="subject">Dyes and dyeing Chemistry</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phw5182.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23674725</field></doc><doc><field name="title">A dual assembly multileaf collimator for radiotherapy</field><field name="creator">Greer, Peter Brian.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 241-250. A multileaf collimator for radiation therapy  has been designed that splits each leaf bank into two vertically displaced assemblies or levels with each level consisting of alternate leaves and leaf spaces. The radiation profiles transmitted for image formation through the collimator  design were investigated to examine their dependence on the collimator  design features.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Cancer Radiotherapy</field><field name="subject">Diagnostic imaging</field><field name="subject">Medical physics</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phg81659.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23674744</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Development of the pulmonary surfactant system in non-mammalian amniotes</field><field name="creator">Johnston, Sonya D. (Sonya Denise)</field><field name="description">"March 2001". Bibliography: leaves 193-238. Relates changes in the development of the pulmonary surfactant system in response to birth strategy, lung morphology and phylogeny in order to determine the extent of conservation in this process, by quantifying the total of phsospholipid, disaturated phospholipid and cholesterol in the lung washings of embryonic and hatchling chickens, oviparous bearded dragons and viviparous sleepy lizards, snapping turtles and green sea turtles throughout the final stages of incubation and gestation.  Finds that the pattern of development of pulmonary surfactant lipids is consistent with that of mammals.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Pulmonary surfactant</field><field name="subject">Birds Development</field><field name="subject">Reptiles Development</field><field name="subject">Lungs Differentiation</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phj737.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23674745</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Maternal undernutrition and fetal blood pressure and the hypothalamo-pituitary adrenal axis in the late gestation fetal sheep</field><field name="creator">Edwards, Lisa J.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 228-257). Aims to determine the impact of maternal undernutrition during late gestation and during the periconceptional and gestational periods on fetal growth, fetal blood pressure and the fetal hypothalamo-pituitary adrenal axis in the sheep.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Fetal malnutrition Complications</field><field name="subject">Malnutrition in pregnancy Complications</field><field name="subject">Pregnancy Nutritional aspects</field><field name="subject">Hypothalamic-pituitary-adrenal axis</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phe2654.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23674870</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Studies of cosmic ray composition using a hybrid fluorescence detector</field><field name="creator">Simpson, K. M. (Kenneth Mark)</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 174-188). Describes several aspects of cosmic ray composition studies using the Utah Fly's Eye and High Resolution Fly's Eye detectors.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Cosmic rays Measurement</field><field name="subject">Fluorimetry</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phs61261.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23674871</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Characterization of nucleoside transport in the intestinal protozoan parasite Giardia intestinalis</field><field name="creator">Davey, Robert Andrew.</field><field name="description">Includes copies of other papers co-authored by the author at end of thesis. Includes bibliographical references (leaves 241-265) A rapid sampling technique has been adapted and used to measure nucleoside transport in a human-derived isolate of the intestinal protozoan parasite Giardia intestinalis (syn. G. lamblia)</field><field name="date">1994</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Giardia lamblia</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phd248.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23675064</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Investigation of the mechanisms involved in cylindrospermopsin  toxicity : hepatocyte culture and reticulocyte lysate studies</field><field name="creator">Froscio, Suzanne M.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 121-139. The aim of this study was to determine the extent to which protein synthesis inhibition, lowered glutathione (GSH) levels and toxin metabolism contribute to the toxicity of cyclindrospermopsin. Both hepatocyte cultures and reticulocyte lysates were utilized as in vitro tools of investigation. The findings imply that the inhibition of protein synthesis by direct action of the toxin cannot be considered a primary cause of hepatocyte cell death over an acute time frame. Cytochrome P450-derived metabolites may play a crucial role in cytotoxicity, and the toxicity process does not appear to involve oxidative damage.</field><field name="date">2002</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SEW</field><field name="subject">Cyanobacteria Health aspects</field><field name="subject">Cyanobacterial toxins Analysis</field><field name="subject">Proteins Synthesis</field><field name="subject">Cyanobacteria Toxicology</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phf938.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23741611</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Subnormal structure of finite soluble groups</field><field name="creator">Wetherell, Chris.</field><field name="description" /><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">ANU</field><field name="subject">Finite groups</field><field name="subject">Solvable groups</field><field name="identifier">http://thesis.anu.edu.au/public/adt-ANU20020607.121248/index.html</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23766278</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Phase transitions of long-chain n-alkanes at interfaces</field><field name="creator">Maeda, Nobuo.</field><field name="description" /><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">ANU</field><field name="subject">Alkanes</field><field name="subject">Phase rule and equilibrium</field><field name="subject">Interfaces (Physical sciences)</field><field name="identifier">http://thesis.anu.edu.au/public/adt-ANU20011203.151921/index.html</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23766545</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Convection, turbulent mixing and salt fingers</field><field name="creator">Wells, Mathew Graeme.</field><field name="description" /><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">ANU</field><field name="subject">Convection (Oceanography)</field><field name="subject">Oceanic mixing</field><field name="subject">Turbulence</field><field name="identifier">http://thesis.anu.edu.au/public/adt-ANU20011212.103012/index.html</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23766557</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The quite revolution : an analysis of the change toward below-replacement-level fertility in Addis Ababa</field><field name="creator">Kinfu Ashagrea, Yohannes.</field><field name="description" /><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">ANU</field><field name="subject">Fertility, Human Ethiopia Addis Ababa</field><field name="subject">Ethiopia Population</field><field name="identifier">http://thesis.anu.edu.au/public/adt-ANU20011218.163822/index.html</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23766623</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The manufacture, characterization and aging of novel high temperature carbon fibre composites</field><field name="creator">Fox, Bronwyn Louise.</field><field name="description" /><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">ANU</field><field name="subject">Heat resistant materials</field><field name="subject">Carbon composites Testing</field><field name="subject">Fibrous composites Testing</field><field name="identifier">http://thesis.anu.edu.au/public/adt-ANU20011207.114246/index.html</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23767081</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Client perceptions : a useful measure of coordination of health care</field><field name="creator">McGuiness, Clare Frances.</field><field name="description" /><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">ANU</field><field name="subject">Public health Australia Evaluation</field><field name="subject">Medical care Australia Evaluation</field><field name="identifier">http://thesis.anu.edu.au/public/adt-ANU20020124.141250/index.html</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23767219</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Dynamics of laboratory models of the wind-driven ocean circulation</field><field name="creator">Kiss, Andrew Elek.</field><field name="description" /><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">ANU</field><field name="subject">Ocean circulation Mathematical models</field><field name="subject">Ocean-atmosphere interaction Mathematical models</field><field name="identifier">http://thesis.anu.edu.au/public/adt-ANU20011018.115707/index.html</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23767602</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Visualisation, navigation and mathematical perception : a visual notation for rational numbers mod 1</field><field name="creator">Tolmie, Julie.</field><field name="description" /><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">ANU</field><field name="subject">Numbers, Rational</field><field name="subject">Fractals</field><field name="subject">Space perception</field><field name="subject">Visual perception</field><field name="subject">Mandelbrot sets</field><field name="identifier">http://thesis.anu.edu.au/public/adt-ANU20020313.101505/index.html</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23767638</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Problems and prospects in cross-cultural interactions in Japanese multinational corporations in Australia</field><field name="creator">Sakurai, Yuka.</field><field name="description" /><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">ANU</field><field name="subject">International business enterprises Australia Management</field><field name="subject">Corporations, Japanese Australia Management</field><field name="subject">Corporate culture Japan</field><field name="subject">Corporate culture Australia</field><field name="subject">Employee attitude surveys Australia</field><field name="subject">Job satisfaction Australia</field><field name="identifier">http://thesis.anu.edu.au/public/adt-ANU20020122.092141/index.html</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23767680</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Molecular biology of "Vibrio cholerae" bacteriophage CP-T1 and its host interactions</field><field name="creator">Guidolin, Angelo.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliography.</field><field name="date">1985</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Vibrio cholerae</field><field name="subject">Bacteriophages</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phg948.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:4246914</field></doc><doc><field name="title">A multimedia system to instruct novice users of online library catalogues</field><field name="creator">Evans, Paul.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliography.</field><field name="date">1996</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">NUWS:W</field><field name="subject">University of Western Sydney, Nepean Dissertations</field><field name="subject">Information retrieval User education</field><field name="subject">Online catalogs User education</field><field name="subject">Reference services (Libraries) Automation</field><field name="subject">Online bibliographic searching</field><field name="subject">Library catalogs and readers</field><field name="subject">Academic libraries Reference services Automation</field><field name="identifier">http://library.nepean.uws.edu.au/about/staff/thesis.html</field><field name="identifier">NBD:23971852</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The representation of places : idiographic and nomothetic explorations of environmental perception and behaviour</field><field name="creator">Olekalns, Mara.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 347-361.</field><field name="date">1985</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Cognition</field><field name="subject">Environmental psychology</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09pho46.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:4302679</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Ecological physiology of malleefowl (`Leipoa ocellata`)</field><field name="creator">Booth, David Terrington.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: v. 1, leaves 189-216 v. 1. [Text] -- v. 2. Figures</field><field name="date">1985</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Malleefowl Physiology</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phb725.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:4302688</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Hume, probability and induction</field><field name="creator">Rowan, Michael.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 397-406.</field><field name="date">1985</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Hume, David, 1711-1776 Philosophy</field><field name="subject">Induction (Logic)</field><field name="subject">Probabilities</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phr877.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:4302693</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Managing multiple dimensions of manufacturing performance - an exploratory study</field><field name="creator">Lillis, Anne M.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references : (p. [37]-40) Drawing on qualitative data collected during semi-structured interviews with 36 profit centre managers in manufacturing firms in Victoria, Australia, this study seeks to explore the mechanisms used to manage multiple manufacturing performance dimensions arising from the pursuit of profit centre strategy.  Where measures capture potentially conflicting influences on the manufacturing cost function, strategy implementation is facilitated by loosening control reactions to cost variances and through explicit attempts to integrate multiple measures.  However, a joint emphasis on performance dimensions relating to manufacturing efficiency and customer responsiveness emerges as problematic.  In contrast, a joint emphasis on quality and efficiency is relatively easily managed.  It is suggested that in the context of responsiveness strategies, the difficulty of designing complete measures inhibits the relevance of performance measurement systems as a facilitator of strategy implementation.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">ANU</field><field name="subject">Performance standards Measurement</field><field name="subject">Production management</field><field name="identifier">http://wff1.ecom.unimelb.edu.au/accwww/research/res_papers.html</field><field name="identifier">http://wff2.ecom.unimelb.edu.au/accwww/research/papers/0200%20ALillis.pdf</field><field name="identifier">http://www1.ecom.unimelb.edu.au/accwww/research/res_papers.html</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24092757</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Using diagnostic controls to maintain and direct the momentum of strategic change - a case study</field><field name="creator">Lawson, Benn.</field><field name="description">"December 2001" Includes bibliographical references : (p. 31-32) Simons (1990) notion of interactive controls has been used in the literature to examine the role of management control systems in facilitating strategic change.  The implications of strategic change for routine diagnostic feedback mechanisms have received less attention.  Drawing on interview and archival data from a single case study of an Australian pump manufacturer, we examine the way diagnostic controls are used in the immediate period following strategic change.  The changes in diagnostic controls are shown not only to align the organization in a self-regulating way to a new strategic direction, but also to promote learning, co-operation and culture change which are integral to, rather than an outcome of the strategic change process.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">ANU</field><field name="subject">Industrial management</field><field name="subject">Strategic planning</field><field name="identifier">http://wff2.ecom.unimelb.edu.au/accwww/research/papers/0201%20BLawson&amp;ALillis.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24092801</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Customer costing responsiveness - an analytical framework</field><field name="creator">Lillis, Anne M.</field><field name="description">"January 2002" Includes bibliographical references: (p. 31-34). The primary purpose of this study is to develop a framework for identifying the primary drivers of the costs of being customer responsive.  The authors' aim is to develop an understanding of the causal drivers of the costs of responsiveness as these costs are considered to be an important input to strategic and tactical decisions.  In developing this framework, the paper links the characteristics of responsive manufacturing from the operations management literature with the insights from studies in the accounting literature relating to the drivers of cost.  The paper attempts to model the cost impact when a firm responds to ad hoc demands involving the product customization, variation in product mix, or changes to delivery schedules.  The costs emerge as a function of the type of responsiveness and the resource capacity management strategy implemented by the firm.  The magnitude and dynamics of market demands and firm response, as well as the inherent flexibility of the firm's resources are seen as influencing the magnitude of the costs of responsiveness. disper</field><field name="date">2002</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">ANU</field><field name="subject">Customer services Econometric models</field><field name="subject">Customer services</field><field name="identifier">http://wff2.ecom.unimelb.edu.au/accwww/research/papers/0202%20ALillis&amp;MAAbernethy.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24092813</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Financial analysts and intangible assets</field><field name="creator">Wyatt, Anne.</field><field name="description">"June 2002" Includes bibliographical references: (p. 30-35). The papers examines the association between the transparency of corporate financial reporting on intangible assets relative to a proxy for total intangible assets, and analyst incentives to follow firms and properties of analysts' earnings forecasts - controlling for endogeneity among these factors. More transparent financial reporting on intangible assets is measured by higher recognition of intangible assets on the balance sheet relative to a proxy variable for total (underlying) intangible assets, market value added which equals equity market value minus book value with intangible assets subtracted. The results suggest (1) a reputation for transparent financial reporting on intangible assets is associated with increased demand for analyst research and thus analyst following incentives; and (2) a reputation for less transparent reporting on intangible assets is associated with higher forecast dispersion and errors due to analysts' greater reliance on their own private information. The study extends research on determinants of analyst following, forecast dispersion and accuracy, and research on the impact of public disclosure on private information acquisition activity.</field><field name="date">2002</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">ANU</field><field name="subject">Finance Accounting</field><field name="subject">Intangible property Accounting</field><field name="identifier">http://wff2.ecom.unimelb.edu.au/accwww/research/papers/0204%20AWyatt&amp;JWong.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24092841</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Capitalising on the potential of cross-sectional field studies for theory refinement in management accounting</field><field name="creator">Lillis, Anne M.</field><field name="description">"January 2002" Includes bibliographical references: (p. 26-28).</field><field name="date">2002</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">ANU</field><field name="subject">Managerial accounting Case studies</field><field name="subject">Managerial accounting</field><field name="identifier">http://wff2.ecom.unimelb.edu.au/accwww/research/papers/0203%20ALillis&amp;JMundy.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24230877</field></doc><doc><field name="title">National review of nursing education : student expectations of nursing education</field><field name="creator">Saltmarsh, David L. W. (David Lloyd William)</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Nursing students Australia Attitudes</field><field name="subject">Nursing Study and teaching Australia Evaluation</field><field name="identifier">http://www.dest.gov.au/highered/nursing/pubs/student_expect/1.htm</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24261302</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The carbon cycle over the last 1000 years inferred from inversion of ice core data</field><field name="creator">Trudinger, Catherine Mary, 1968-</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">VS:ATP</field><field name="subject">Carbon cycle (Biogeochemistry)</field><field name="identifier">http://www.dar.csiro.au/publications/Trudinger_2001a0.htm</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24385057</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Simulating the effects of following distance on a high-flow freeway</field><field name="creator">Lierkamp, Darren.</field><field name="description">"CP830 Research Project and Thesis 2". Includes bibliographical references (p. 80-93) Electronic reproduction.[S.l. :s.n.],2003.Electronic data.Mode of access: World Wide Web.System requirements: Adobe Acrobat reader software for PDF files.Access restricted to institutions with a subscription.</field><field name="date" /><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">VMOU</field><field name="subject">Traffic flow Mathematical models</field><field name="subject">Traffic accidents Mathematical models</field><field name="subject">Traffic accidents Costs Mathematical models</field><field name="subject">Express highways Mathematical models</field><field name="identifier">http://images.lib.monash.edu.au/ts/theses/Lierkamp.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24430412</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The basis of variation in the size and composition of grape berries</field><field name="creator">Gray, John D.</field><field name="description">"Department of Horticulture, Viticulture and Oenology, Faculty of Agriculture and Natural Resource Sciences, The University of Adelaide, Waite Campus, Glen Osmond S.A." Bibliography: leaves 136-149 This investigated focussed on selected aspects of berry development and ripening that were subject to variation. Shiraz and Chardonnay were chosen as experimental varieties because these cultivars presented a large range of variability in the field. The extent of the variation within each of the recorded berry parameters was assessed using the coefficient of variation (CV), a unitless measure of sample variability relative to the sample mean, ideally suited to comparative studies.</field><field name="date">2002</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">NCSU:W</field><field name="subject">University of Adelaide. Dissertations</field><field name="subject">Viticulture</field><field name="subject">Grapes Growth</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phg7794.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24477376</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Phenotypic and genetic parameters for the S.A. Strongwool merino strain with an emphasis on skin characters as early indicators of wool productivity</field><field name="creator">Hill, Jane Adair.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 325-341. Skin and fleece measurements were recorded at different ages for both male and female sheep from the Turretfield Merino Resource Flock and used to estimate the heritability of each trait and the phenotypic and genetic correlations among and between the skin and fleece traits. Generally, the heritability of each trait was high, which indicates that both the fleece and skin traits should respond well to selection.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">NAD:TR</field><field name="subject">Turretfield Research Centre</field><field name="subject">Merino sheep Australia Genetics</field><field name="subject">Merino sheep Breeding Australia</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phh6463.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24509045</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Assessment of the antiprotozoal activity of some tubulin inhibitors following cyclodextrin complexation</field><field name="creator">Menon, Kathleen I.</field><field name="description">Thesis submitted to the Division of Veterinary and Biomedical Sciences. Bibliography: leaves 237-283.</field><field name="date">2002</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">WMDU</field><field name="subject">Protozoa, Pathogenic</field><field name="subject">Cyclodextrins</field><field name="subject">Microtubules</field><field name="subject">Tubulins</field><field name="subject">Protozoan diseases</field><field name="identifier">http://wwwlib.murdoch.edu.au/adt/admin/view/adt-MU20040820.133836</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24523425</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Ideals, myths and realities a postmodern analysis of moral-ethical decision-making and professional ethics in social work practice</field><field name="creator">Asquith, Merrylyn.</field><field name="description">Electronic reproduction.</field><field name="date">2002</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SSHC</field><field name="subject">Social workers Professional ethics</field><field name="subject">Social work education</field><field name="identifier">http://www.dhs.sa.gov.au/dhs-library/documents/ideals,-myths-and-realities.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24552294</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Reflective qualities of the artistic creative process and chaos theory a study of their relationship and the implications for art education and teaching</field><field name="creator">Regent, Barbara.</field><field name="description">Faculty of Education. Includes bibliographical references (leaves 194-222)</field><field name="date">2002</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">NNCU:A</field><field name="subject">Creative thinking</field><field name="subject">Art Study and teaching</field><field name="subject">Consciousness</field><field name="subject">Creative ability</field><field name="subject">Chaotic behavior in systems</field><field name="subject">Art in education</field><field name="subject">Creation (Literary, artistic, etc.)</field><field name="identifier">http://www.newcastle.edu.au/sevices/library/adt/public/adt-NNCU20030306.101051/index.html</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24577113</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Exploring the use of interactive voice response as a population health tool</field><field name="creator">Corkrey, Stephen Ross.</field><field name="description">School of Medical Practice and Population Health. CD contains supplementary materials. Includes bibliographical references (leaves 266-318)</field><field name="date">2002</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">NNCU:A</field><field name="subject">Health promotion</field><field name="subject">Data collection Methods</field><field name="subject">Medical informatics</field><field name="subject">Health promotion</field><field name="subject">Public health</field><field name="subject">Preventive health services</field><field name="subject">Health Information services</field><field name="subject">Telephone surveys Evaluation</field><field name="subject">Telephone surveys Data processing</field><field name="subject">Health surveys Evaluation</field><field name="subject">Speech processing systems</field><field name="identifier">http://www.newcastle.edu.au/services/library/adt/public/adt-NNCU20030527.052149/index.html</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24588480</field></doc><doc><field name="title">From atomic energy to nuclear science : a history of the Australian Atomic Energy Commission</field><field name="creator">Binnie, Anna-Eugenia.</field><field name="description">Also published on CD-ROM. Includes bibliographical references.</field><field name="date">2003</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">NLHR</field><field name="subject">Australian Atomic Energy Commission History</field><field name="subject">Nuclear reactors New South Wales Lucas Heights</field><field name="subject">Electronic books</field><field name="subject">Nuclear energy Government policy Australia</field><field name="identifier">http://www.ansto.gov.au/libsite/Fulltext/Binnie_atomic-energy.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24635607</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Theorising information use : managers and their work</field><field name="creator">Kirk, Joyce, 1945-</field><field name="description" /><field name="date">2002</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">NTSM</field><field name="subject">Information resources management</field><field name="subject">Corporations Information services Management</field><field name="identifier">http://adt.lib.uts.edu.au/public/adt-NTSM20030410.145632/index.html</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24693621</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The "adequacy of their attention": gender-bias &amp; the introductory law course in Australian law schools</field><field name="creator">Ward, Helen, 1963-</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 220-229) Considers to what extent feminist theoretical and critical perspectives have been incorporated into law. A law course or law textbook that uncritically presents legal doctrines, or representations of men's and women's social roles, risks adopting and perpetuating the unstated point-of-view of a particular cultural group in society. Argues for a legal education that has an open self-consciousness of the culturally specific and inevitably partial point-of-view of the law and, consequently, a conscious recognition of the unavoidable point-of-view of legal education.</field><field name="date">1999</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Feminist jurisprudence</field><field name="subject">Sex discrimination in criminal justice administration</field><field name="subject">Practice of law</field><field name="subject">Law Study and teaching (Higher) Australia</field><field name="subject">Education, Higher Australia</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09LM/09lmw258.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24717371</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Molecular diversity between anastomosis groups of Rhizoctonia solani : a thesis submitted in fulfilment of the requirements for the degree of Doctor of Philosophy in the Department of Animal Sciences at the University of Adelaide</field><field name="creator">Matthew, Jamie Scott.</field><field name="description">Journal article co-authored by the author inserted at end (Plant pathology (1991) 40, 67-77) Includes bibliographical references (leaves 124-167) Describes the isolation of antibody and DNA probes which vary in their reaction to different anastomosis groups of Rhizoctonia solani. Evidence is presented to show that isolates from anastomosis group 8 are biochemically distinct from isolates in other anastomosis groups found in South Australia.</field><field name="date">1992</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Rhizoctonia solani</field><field name="subject">Rhizoctonia South Australia Molecular aspects</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phm437.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24717469</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Chocolate spot of faba beans in South Australia</field><field name="creator">Dennis, Jeremy Ian.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 81-100. Entry of inoculum into a crop and disease development in the crop cannot be prevented because spores are airborne and there is a lack of highly resistant varieties. This makes complete control of chocolate spot unlikely. It should however, be possible to improve current levels of disease control through the integration of the  factors identified in the study.</field><field name="date">1991</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Beans Diseases and pests Australia</field><field name="subject">Field crops Diseases and pests Australia</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09A/09ad411pdf.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24717599</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Investigation of galactosyltransferase and &#273;-lactalbumin-like proteins in mammalian reproductive tracts</field><field name="creator">Tang, Yulu.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 174-191). Studies the functions of galactosyltransferase (GalTase) and &#273;-lactalbumin (&#273;-lac) in mammalian reproduction. Investigates whether GalTase and &#273;-lac-like proteins are widely present in epididymal plasma of various mammalian species and their function in reproduction; whether GalTase is also present in luminal plasma of the female reproductive tract, where sperm capacitation and fertilization occur; and, whether GalTase is also the sperm's receptor for zona in other species than mouse.</field><field name="date">1993</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09pht164.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24717603</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Nitrogen assimilation by rumen microorganisms: a study of the assimilation of ammonia by rumen bacteria in vivo and in vitro</field><field name="creator">Edwards, Nicholas John.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves [259]-290) Investigates nitrogen assimilation and metabolism in rumen bacteria with the object of understanding the basic process and their controls.</field><field name="date">1991</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Rumen fermentation</field><field name="subject">Ruminants Feeding and feeds</field><field name="subject">Rumen Microbiology</field><field name="subject">Nitrogen Metabolism</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phe2657.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24717640</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The inheritance and control of isolated pigmented wool fibres in merino sheep</field><field name="creator">Fleet, M. R. (Malcolm R.)</field><field name="description">Copies of author's previously published works inserted. Includes bibliographical references (leaves 222-258). Researches the occurence and inheritance of isolated melanin pigmented wool fibres and macroscopic pigmentation in Merino sheep. The mode of inheritance of key indicators (pigmented leg fibres and pigmented birthcoat halo-hair) of isolated pigmented wool fibres is investigated and confirms an association between isolated pigmented fibres in hogget Merino fleeces and the presence and degree of types of remnant macroscopic fibre pigmentation. These associations could be exploited to improve wool quality in relation to dark fibre risk.</field><field name="date">1997</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Agricultural Research Station (Trangie, N.S.W.)</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09A/09af594.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24717650</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Variation in alfalfa mosaic virus with special reference to its immunochemical properties</field><field name="creator">Hajimorad, Mohammad Reza.</field><field name="description">Includes Appendix listing other publications by the author. Includes bibliographical references (leaves 134-181). Alfalfa mosaic virus was isolated from lucerne (Medicago sativa) plants with a variety of disease symptoms. Experiments showed that each isolate was biologically distinct and that the host range and symptomatology of each isolate was affected by the environmental condition.</field><field name="date">1990</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Alfalfa Diseases and pests</field><field name="subject">RNA viruses Genetics</field><field name="subject">Cucumoviruses</field><field name="subject">Viral genetics</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phh154.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24717784</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Factors affecting sow and gilt efficiency in commercial piggeries in Zambia : a thesis submitted in fulfilment of the requirements for admission to the degree of Master of Agricultural Science of the University of Adelaide</field><field name="creator">Crafter, S. A.</field><field name="description">Questionnaires (Survey into the commercial pig industry of Zambia covering the 1983-1984 financial year ; Sow card survey ; and, Abbatoir survey form) included as appendices in pocket in back. Includes bibliographical references (leaves 219-251) The research looked for simple answers to simple problems in the Zambian commercial pig industry. Due to logistical difficulties of working in a developing country it was designed to be a project that could be carried out in the third world and which did not involve reliance on sophisticated machinery or techniques.</field><field name="date">1992</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Pork industry and trade Zambia</field><field name="subject">Swine Research Zambia</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09A/09ac8846.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24717900</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Variation among cucumber mosaic virus (CMV) isolates and their interaction with plants</field><field name="creator">Wahyuni, Wiwiek Sri.</field><field name="description">Includes appendix containing journal publications co-authored by the author. Includes bibliographical references (leaves 130-151). Eighteen strains of Cucumber mosaic virus, including forteen from Australia, two from the USA, and two from Japan were used in this study.</field><field name="date">1992</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Cucumber mosaic virus Genetics</field><field name="subject">RNA viruses Genetics</field><field name="subject">Cucumoviruses</field><field name="subject">Viral genetics</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phw137.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24717902</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The epidemiology of cucumber mosaic virus in narrow-leafed lupins (Lupinus angustifolius) in South Australia</field><field name="creator">Geering, Andrew D.W.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 147-171). Studies factors affecting the rate of epidemic progress of cucumber mosaic virus in Lupinus angustifolius.</field><field name="date">1992</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Alfalfa Diseases and pests South Australia</field><field name="subject">Cucumber mosaic virus Genetics</field><field name="subject">RNA viruses Genetics</field><field name="subject">Cucumoviruses</field><field name="subject">Viral genetics</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phg298.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24717904</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Short term effects of stress hormones on cell division rate in wool follicles : a thesis submitted in fulfilment of the requirements for the degree of Doctor of Philosophy</field><field name="creator">Scobie, David Roger.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 183-207) A local intradermal technique using colchicine to estimate cell division rate in wool follicles is refined and used throughout the thesis. Statistical methods used to analyse data obtained with this method are described and discussed. The implications of the findings are of great significance to research into the influence of physiological changes on wool production, and suggest experiments should be conducted under controlled environmental conditions, with a minimum of stress imposed on the animals.</field><field name="date">1992</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Wool Australia Growth</field><field name="subject">Wool industry Australia Quality control</field><field name="subject">Catecholamines Physiological effect</field><field name="subject">Sheep Australia Physiology</field><field name="subject">Stress (Physiology)</field><field name="subject">Neurosecretion</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phs421.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24717920</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Pathology and distribution in the host of pea seed-borne mosaic virus</field><field name="creator">Ligat, Julio S.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 82-92). Five isolates of pea seed-borne mosaic virus were compared by host range and symptomatology on 16 pisum sativum cultivars lines, 21 lines of Lathyrus and Lens spp. and several indicator species</field><field name="date">1993</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Peas Diseases and pests</field><field name="subject">RNA viruses Genetics</field><field name="subject">Cucumoviruses</field><field name="subject">Viral genetics</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phl723.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24717923</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Effects of insulin-like growth factors (IGFS) on recovery from gut resection in rats : a thesis submitted to the University of Adelaide, South Australia for the degree of Doctor of Philosophy</field><field name="creator">Lemmey, Andrew Bruce.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 159-213) Shows that IGF-I peptides are effective in diminishing post-surgical catabolism and enhancing adaptive gut hyperplasia in rats recovering from massive small bowel resection.</field><field name="date">1993</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Insulin-like growth factor I Physiology</field><field name="subject">Intestine, Small Immunology</field><field name="subject">Gastrointestinal hormones Physiology</field><field name="subject">Digestive organs Surgery</field><field name="subject">Rats Physiology</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phl554.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24717927</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Induction of mitogenesis and cell-cell adhesion by porcine seminal plasma</field><field name="creator">Hadjisavas, Michael.</field><field name="description">Includes list of publications by the author. Includes bibliographical references (leaves 103-123) Evaluates the nature of the interactions occurring between semen and cells of the uterus that occur following mating in pigs. Describes a novel ability of porcine seminal plasma to induce dose dependent cell-cell adhesion and mitogenesis amongst peripheral blood lymphocytes in vitro.</field><field name="date">1992</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Swine Reproduction</field><field name="subject">Spermatozoa Physiology</field><field name="subject">Cell adhesion</field><field name="subject">Cells Motility</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phh1293.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24717928</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Calibration of numerical models with application to groundwater flow in the Willunga Basin, South Australia</field><field name="creator">Rasser, Paul Edward.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: 80-82. Electronic publication; full text available in PDF format; abstract in HTML format. The process of calibrating a numerical model is examined in this thesis with an application to the flow of groundwater in the Willunga Basin in South Australia. The calibration process involves estimating unknown parameters of the numerical model so that the output obtained from the model is comparable with data that is observed in the field. Three methods for calibrating numerical models are discussed, these being the steepest descent method, the nonlinear least squares method, and a new method called the response function method. Electronic reproduction.[Australia] :Australian Digital Theses Program,2001.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Groundwater South Australia Willunga Basin</field><field name="subject">Mathematical models</field><field name="identifier">http://thesis.library.adelaide.edu.au/public/adt-SUA20030414.111541/index.html</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24717980</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Studies on the relationship between characteristics of ram semen and fertility</field><field name="creator">Quintana Casares, Pablo Ignacio.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 274-316) Examines several aspects of male reproduction in the sheep, and how these are related to fertility in the female when semen is introduced by natural mating or artificial insemination.</field><field name="date">1991</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Sheep Reproduction</field><field name="subject">Sheep Fertility</field><field name="subject">Artificial insemination</field><field name="subject">Semen</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phq7.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24717986</field></doc><doc><field name="title">IGF transfer from blood to tissue: comparison of IGF-I with analogs that bind poorly to binding proteins, using a vascular perfusion model : a thesis submitted to the University of Adelaide, South Australia, for the degree of Doctor of Philosophy</field><field name="creator">Lord, Andrew P.D. (Andrew Peter Duncan)</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 188-217) Insulin-like growth factor-I circulates at high concentrations in blood, mainly complexed with IGF-binding proteins. The main objective of the thesis is to determine the general role played by plasma IGF-binding proteins in the regulation of IGF transfer from blood to tissues.</field><field name="date">1993</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Insulin-like growth factor binding protein</field><field name="subject">Insulin-like growth factor I Physiology</field><field name="subject">Blood proteins Physiology</field><field name="subject">Sheep Physiology</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phl866.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24718032</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Finite difference methods for advection and diffusion</field><field name="creator">Trojan, Alice von.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 158-163). Concerns the development of high-order finite-difference methods on a uniform rectangular grid for advection and diffuse problems with smooth variable coefficients. This technique has been successfully applied to variable-coefficient advection and diffusion problems. Demonstrates that the new schemes may readily be incorporated into multi-dimensional problems by using locally one-dimensional techniques, or that they may be used in process splitting algorithms to solve complicatef time-dependent partial differential equations.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Finite differences</field><field name="subject">Differential equations, Partial Numerical solutions</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phv948.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24718459</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Effects of wastewater effluent on macrobenthic infaunal communities at Christies Beach, South Australia</field><field name="creator">Loo, Maylene G. K. (Maylene Geok Kuan)</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 136-154) Aims to determine the effects of an outfall discharging secondarily treated wastewater effluent on benthic communities at Christies Beach with the specific objectives of: characterising the physical, biological and chemical environment of Gulf St Vincent and the study area region; ascertaining the extent to which effluent outfall has affected the macrobenthic infaunal community structure; characterising the structure of macrobenthic infaunal communities in the near shore water of the Adelaide metropolitan coast; and, determining the functional response through measurements of sediment community respiration to these changes.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Benthic animals South Australia Christies Beach Observations</field><field name="subject">Aquatic invertebrates South Australia Christies Beach Observations</field><field name="subject">Sewage disposal in the ocean Environmental aspects South Australia Christies Beach</field><field name="subject">Marine ecology South Australia Christies Beach</field><field name="subject">Marine pollution South Australia Christies Beach</field><field name="subject">Environmental impact analysis South Australia Christies Beach</field><field name="subject">Christies Beach (S. Aust.)</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phl8625.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24718549</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Biological and molecular variation among isolates of pea seed borne mosaic virus</field><field name="creator">Torok, Valeria Anna.</field><field name="description">Corrigendum inserted at the back. Includes bibliographical references (leaves 133-158). Ch. 1. General introduction -- ch. 2. General materials and methods -- ch. 3. Biological characterisation of Australian PSbMV isolates -- ch. 4. Developing nucleic acid based diagnostics for PSbMV -- ch. 5. Detection of PSbMV isolates by RT-PCR and RFLP analysis -- ch. 6. Developing an internal control for PSbMV RT-PCR -- ch. 7. Molecular analysis of the PSbMV VPG -- ch. 8. PSbMV sequence and phylogenetic analysis -- ch. 9. General discussion Sixteen pea seed borne mosaic virus (PSbMV) isolates were collected between 1995 and 1998. These isolates were biologically distinct yet serologically indistinguishable. The conclusion is that PSbMV is widespread and occurs at a low incidence in Australia. Reports sequence information on new isolates of PSbMV which has allowed genomic regions to be identified which distinguish PSbMV pathotypes and isolates; and, to the development of PSbMV nucleic acid hybridisation and RT-PCR assays.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Peas Diseases and pests</field><field name="subject">Plant viruses Genetics</field><field name="subject">Virus-induced enzymes</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09pht686.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24718578</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Modelling structural and policy changes in the world wine market into the 21st century</field><field name="creator">Berger, Nicholas.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references. Addresses the question of what an economic model of the world wine market suggests will happen to wine production, consumption, trade and prices in various regions in the early 21st century. A subsidiary issue is what difference would global or European regional wine liberalisation make to that outlook, according to such a model. Accompanying CD-ROM comprises spreadsheet written by Nick Berger, November 2000, for the Windows and Office97 versions of Excel; a seven region world wine model (WWM7) - base version projecting the world wine market 1996-2005 as a non-linear Armington model. System requirements for accompanying CD-ROM: IBM compatible computer ; Microsoft Excel 97 or later.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Wine and wine making Statistics</field><field name="subject">Wine industry Forecasting</field><field name="subject">Wine and wine making Economic conditions Econometric models</field><field name="subject">Commercial policy Econometric models</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09ECM/09ecmb496.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24718639</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The following (walking) ability of the neonatal lamb</field><field name="creator">Oppong-Anane, Kwame.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 276-2970. Investigations presented involve 18 hour to 5 day old South Australian merino lambs. Some twin lambs were available for comparative studies. Examines the relationship between the strength of ewe-lamb bond and the lamb's ability to follow the mother, the energy availability and usage in the lamb, particularly for locomotion, and the metabolic and cardiorespiratory responses to locomotion.</field><field name="date">1991</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09pho62.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24718832</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The Blood-brain barrier in normal and pathological conditions</field><field name="creator">Zhu, Chunni.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 318-367. Examines the blood-brain barrier in normal and pathological conditions induced by intravascular and extravascular insults. Intravascular insults were induced by administration of Clostridium perfringens prototoxin; extravascular insults were induced by an impact acceleration model for closed head injury to induce traumatic brain injury. Also examines the integrity of the blood-brain barrier ultrastructurally and by its ability to exclude endogenous and exogenous tracers.  Also studies the expression of 2 blood-brain barrier specific proteins, endothelial barrier antigen (EBA) and glucose transporter 1 (GLUT1)</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Blood-brain barrier Physiology</field><field name="subject">Blood-brain barrier Pathophysiology</field><field name="subject">Blood-brain barrier Ultrastructure</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phz637.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24718880</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Three-dimensional tide and surge modelling and layered particle tracking techniques applied to Southern Australian coastal seas</field><field name="creator">Grzechnik, Marcus Paul.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 197-205. Electronic publication; full text available in PDF format; abstract in HTML format. This thesis reports the development, testing, and application of computer programs for simulating Lagrangian-Stochastic particle dispersion in coastal seas, with particular application to tide and storm induced dispersion in South Australian seas. Electronic reproduction.[Australia] :Australian Digital Theses Program,2001.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="identifier">http://thesis.library.adelaide.edu.au/public/adt-SUA20010213.232311/index.html</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24718884</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Mathematical and computational techniques for predicting the squat of ships</field><field name="creator">Gourlay, Tim.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: p. 145-148 Electronic publication; full text available in PDF format; abstract in HTML format. This thesis deals with the squat of a moving ship, that is, the downward displacement and angle of trim caused by its forward motion. The aim is to be able to predict accurately the squat of any ship at any given speed and water depth. (introduction) Electronic reproduction.[Australia] :Australian Digital Theses Program,2001.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Shipping Mathematical models</field><field name="identifier">http://thesis.library.adelaide.edu.au/public/adt-SUA20010217.015116/index.html</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24718885</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Active control of sound in a small single engine aircraft cabin with virtual error sensors</field><field name="creator">Kestell, Colin D. (Colin David)</field><field name="description">Bibliography: p. 199-207. Electronic publication; full text available in PDF format; abstract in HTML format. Describes the basis of a theoretical and experimental project, directed at the design and evaluation of a practical active noise control system suitable for a single light engine aircraft. The performance of virtual sensors were evaluated both analytically and experimentally in progressively more complex environments to identify their capabilities and limitations. Electronic reproduction.[Australia] :Australian Digital Theses Program,2001.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Aircraft cabins Noise Measurement</field><field name="subject">Noise control Mathematical models</field><field name="subject">Acoustical engineering</field><field name="subject">Computer input-output equipment Design Data processing</field><field name="identifier">http://thesis.library.adelaide.edu.au/public/adt-SUA20010216.164243/index.html</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24718892</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Sacred worlds : an analysis of mystical mastery of North Indian Faqirs</field><field name="creator">Saniotis, Arthur.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 317-341) An ethnography of fakirs' mystical mastery based on fieldwork at the thirteenth century Muslim shrine of Nizamuddin Auliya.</field><field name="date">2002</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Ni&#7827;&#257;mudd&#299;n Auliy&#257;, 1236-1325</field><field name="subject">Fakirs Social aspects India New Delhi</field><field name="subject">Mysticism India</field><field name="subject">Sufism India</field><field name="subject">Islamic shrines India New Delhi</field><field name="subject">Islam Social aspects India New Delhi</field><field name="subject">New Delhi (India) Buildings, structures, etc</field><field name="subject">New Delhi (India) Religious life and customs</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phs227.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24718896</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Women drinking in early modern England</field><field name="creator">Cast, Andrea Snowden.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 320-415) Investigates female drinking patterns and how they impacted on women's lives in the sixteenth and seventeenth centuries in early modern England. Deals with female drinking as a site of contention between insubordinate women and the dominant paradigm of male expectations about drinking and drunkeness. Female drinking patterns integrated drinking and drunkeness into women's lives in ways that enhanced bonding with their female friends, even if it inconvenienced their husbands and male authorities. Drunken sociability empowered women.</field><field name="date">2002</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Women Alcohol use Social aspects England</field><field name="subject">Women Social conditions England History 16th century</field><field name="subject">Women Social conditions England History 17th century</field><field name="subject">Drinking of alcoholic beverages England History 16th century</field><field name="subject">Drinking of alcoholic beverages England History 17th century</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phc346.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24719005</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The importance of disciplining the choice of policy instrument to the effectiveness of the GATT as international law disciplining agricultural trade policies / Brett Gerard Williams</field><field name="creator">Williams, Brett Gerard.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves p. i-xxxii) Pt. 1. Is there a link between the problem with agriculture under GATT rules and policy choice under GATT rules? -- pt. 2. The economic and political significance of distinctions between policy instruments -- pt. 3. The application of the pre-Uruguay Round GATT to agriculture -- pt. 4. The Uruguay Round rules on agriculture -- pt. 5. The thesis and its importance Seeks an answer to the legal difficulties in applying GATT to agriculture</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (Organization)</field><field name="subject">Uruguay Round, (1987-1994)</field><field name="subject">Tariff on farm produce</field><field name="subject">Produce trade xGovernment policy</field><field name="subject">Agriculture and state</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phw72122.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24719012</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Controls on reservoir development and quality in a glacial sequence; a study of the late palaeozoic, Cooper Basin South Australia and Queensland, Australia : thesis submitted to the University of Adelaide in fullfillment [sic] of the requirement for the Degree of Doctor of Philosophy, July 2000</field><field name="creator">Cubitt, Chris.</field><field name="description">At head of title: National Centre for Petroleum Geology and Geophysics. CD-ROM contains Appendices (1-10) in PDF. Includes copies of papers co-authored by the author. Includes bibliographical references (leaves [471]-499 in vol. 2) Studies the provenance and diagenesis of the Merrimelia Formation in South Australia and Queensland; a complex mosaic of glacial facies in which the Tirrawarra Sandstone and Merrimelia Formation exhibit an interfingering relationship, and defines the relationship further. Indicates that the Tirrawarra Sandstone should be included in the Merrimelia Formation as a "facies type" as both the Merrimelia and Tirrawarra sediments form an integrated suite of sediments. System requirements for accompanying CD-ROM: Macintosh or IBM compatible computer with Windows NT. Other requirements: Adobe Acrobat Reader.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Facies (Geology) Cooper Basin (Qld. and S. Aust.)</field><field name="subject">Rocks, Sedimentary Cooper Basin (Qld. and S. Aust.)</field><field name="subject">Sandstone Cooper Basin (Qld. and S. Aust.)</field><field name="subject">Sedimentation and deposition Cooper Basin (Qld. and S. Aust.)</field><field name="subject">Unconformities (Geology) South Australia Tirrawarra Field</field><field name="subject">Sedimentary structures South Australia Tirrawarra Field</field><field name="subject">Cooper Basin (Qld. and S. Aust.)</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phc962.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24719035</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The root lesion nematode, Pratylenchus neglectus, in field crops in South Australia</field><field name="creator">Taylor, Sharyn Patricia.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 241-25). Aims to evaluate sampling procedures; assess the extent and magnitude of yield loss caused by Pratylenchus neglectus; assess the population dynamics of Pratylenchus neglectus in cereals; determine whether resistance occurs in field crops; and, assess whether variation occurs between geographically isolated species of Pratylenchus neglectus</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Pratylenchus</field><field name="subject">Field crops Disease and pest resistance Genetic aspects</field><field name="subject">Nematode diseases of plants Genetic aspects</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09pht2462.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24719037</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Re-thinking the 'migrant community' : a study of Latin American migrants and refugees in Adelaide</field><field name="creator">Cohen, Erez.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 259-270) Based on 18-months fieldwork, 1997-1999, in various organisations, social clubs and radio programs that were constructed by participants and 'outsiders' as an expression of a local migrant community. Attempts to answer and challenge what it means to be a Latin American in Adelaide and in what sense Latin American migrants and refugees in Adelaide can be spoken about as members of an 'ethnic/migrant community' in relation to the official multiculturalism discourse and popular representations of migrants in Australia.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Latin Americans South Australia Ethnic identity</field><field name="subject">Pluralism (Social sciences) Case studies</field><field name="subject">Multiculturalism</field><field name="subject">Ethnicity South Australia Social aspects</field><field name="subject">South Australia Emigration and immigration</field><field name="subject">South Australia Foreign population</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phc6782.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24719088</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Characterisation of the molecular interactions between insulin-like growth factors and their binding proteins</field><field name="creator">Lucic, Melinda Robin.</field><field name="description">Addenda inserted in back. Includes bibliographical references (leaves 139-160) Assesses the importance of amino acids 221 to 236 of bIGFBP-2 for IGF binding activity, by creating amino acid substitutions.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Insulin-like growth factor-binding proteins Molecular aspects</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phl9375.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24719313</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Investigations of Centrosema mosaic, a hitherto undescribed virus  of Crotalaria spp. in Papua and New Guinea</field><field name="creator">Velsen, Reuben John van.</field><field name="description">Typescript; author's name is corrected in pen on t.p. Includes bibliographical references (leaves 52-55). A study has been made of an undescribed virus disease, Centrosema mosaic. Field observations on its occurence, ecology, symptoms, and host range, together with experimental data on mechanical, insect and other methods of transmission are recorded.</field><field name="date">1959</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Crotalaria Diseases and pests Papua New Guinea</field><field name="subject">RNA viruses Genetics</field><field name="subject">Cucumoviruses</field><field name="subject">Viral genetics</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09A/09av28.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24719475</field></doc><doc><field name="title">A parapsychological investigation of the theory of psychopraxia : experimental and theoretical researches into an alternative theory explaining normal and paranormal phenomena</field><field name="creator">Storm, Lance.</field><field name="description">Published articles by the author appended to thesis. Bibliography: p. 288-315. Describes a series of four experiments which were conducted to test the theory of psychopraxia. The thesis is an investigation of the theory from the perspective of paranormal phenomena only. It is argued that the theory of psychopraxia is important to the field of parapsychology because it offers (a) a philosophical critique on taken-for-granted assumptions about the nature of the paranormal, (b) relatively unambiguous terminology, and (c) a process-oriented approach to investigations of the paranormal by concentrating on conditions deemed necessary in bringing about paranormal effects. The thesis concludes that, in its current form, the psychopraxia model needs clarification of its most crucial concepts ("self", "pro-attitude" and "necessary conditions") before it can be regarded as a workable theory.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Parapsychology Investigation</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phs885.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24719664</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Fictocritical sentences</field><field name="creator">Robb, Simon.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 166-168). CD-ROMs comprise: Appendix A. Family values: fictocritical sentences -- appendix C. Reforming the boy: fictocritical sentences Primarily enacts a fictocritical mapping of local cultural events essentially concerned with crime and trauma in Adelaide. The fictocritical treatment of these events simulates their unresolved or traumatised condition. A secondary concern is the relationship between electronic writing (hypertext) and fictocriticism.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Contemporary, The, in literature</field><field name="subject">Crime Fiction Technique</field><field name="subject">Australian literature History and criticism</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phr631.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24719678</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Study of limiting factors and methods of optical phase conjugation by stimulated Brillouin scattering</field><field name="creator">Anikeev, Igor&#697; Yu.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 205-227) A study of phase conjugation by stimulated Brillouin scattering is presented with emphasis on the limiting factors, such as aperture and polarization losses, spatial coherence and saturation of the incident wave on the quality of phase conjugation, as well as the application of stimulated Brillouin scattering to loop phase-cojugated mirror and intracavity-SBS-cell-phase-conjugated oscillator.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Optical phase conjugation</field><field name="subject">Brillouin scattering</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09pha597.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24719742</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The effect of fertiliser management practices on soil organic matter production in the semi-arid areas : a field and modelling approach</field><field name="creator">Georgis, Kidane.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 155-169. Studies the effect of nitrogen fertilizer on dry matter production under differing watering regimes. Investigates the accuracy of different crop and soil organic matter models for predicting crop yield, nitrogen uptake and changes in soil organic carbon and nitrogen. Compares the  models with data from long-term field experiments on wheat in Australia and sorghum in Ethiopia. Finds that a higher crop yield and better nitrogen and water utilisation can be achieved if addition of nitrogen fertilizer is balanced with soil water.</field><field name="date">1997</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Nitrogen fertilizers Arid regions</field><field name="subject">Crop yield Arid regions Computer simulation</field><field name="subject">Soils Arid regions Composition Computer simulation</field><field name="subject">Humus Arid regions Computer simulation</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09AFP/09afpg352.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24719826</field></doc><doc><field name="title">A predictive model of sport sponsorship renewal in Australia</field><field name="creator">Farrelly, Francis John.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 231-291. This thesis investigates key drivers of sponsorship renewal. The market orientation of sponsors, and their perception of their sponsored entity's (property's) market orientation, are analysed as antecedents of the trust invested by sponsors in the relationship, the level of commitment they exhibit and both the economic and non-economic satisfaction they derive from it. Sponsor economic and non-economic satisfaction and their commitment to the relationship are considered to be the ultimate drivers of the decision to renew. The argument is presented that sponsorship is a form of strategic or co-marketing alliance. The Australian Football League, the leading sponsorship property in Australia, is investigated in the empirical part of the thesis.</field><field name="date">2002</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Australian Football League Finance</field><field name="subject">Sports sponsorship Australia</field><field name="subject">Corporate sponsorship Australia</field><field name="subject">Relationship marketing Australia</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phf245.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24719936</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Product innovation and differentiation, intra-industry trade and growth : a thesis submitted in fulfilment of the requirements for the degree of Doctor of Philosophy</field><field name="creator">Peak, Geoffrey Colin.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliograhical references (leaves 239-251) Concerned with the influence that the production of innovative goods has on the economic growth rate of a country. Proposes that amongst the developed economies, the higher the level of production of innovative goods within a country, the higher the GDP growth rate, all else being equal.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">New products Economic aspects</field><field name="subject">Industrial productivity Management</field><field name="subject">Technological innovations Economic aspects</field><field name="subject">Economic development</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09php357.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24719937</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Production ecology and ecophysiology of turf algal communities on a temperate reef (West Island, South Australia)</field><field name="creator">Copertino, Margareth.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 235-258). Estimates the primary production and investigates the photosynthetic performance of temperate turfs at West Island, off the coast of South Australia. These communities play a fundamental role in reef ecology, being the main source of food for grazers, both fishes and invertebrates. Turfs also have an important function in benthic algal community dynamics, being the first colonizers on disturbed and bare substratum.</field><field name="date">2002</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Algae South Australia West Island</field><field name="subject">Algae Physiology</field><field name="subject">Algal populations South Australia West Island</field><field name="subject">Photosynthesis Environmental aspects South Australia West Island</field><field name="subject">Reefs Environmental aspects South Australia West Island</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phc782.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24719940</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Purification, identification and characterisation of signals directing embryonic stem (ES) cell differentiation : a thesis submitted to the University of Adelaide for the degree of Doctor of Philosophy</field><field name="creator">Bettess, Michael David.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 142-168) Aim was the purification and identification of the early primitive ectoderm-like (EPL) cell induction signals within the medium conditioned by the human hepatocellular carcinoma cell line HepG2 and the localisation of the signals that induce EPL cell and primitive ectoderm formation.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Embryonic stem cells</field><field name="subject">Liver Cancer Diagnosis</field><field name="subject">Cell differentiation</field><field name="subject">Biochemical markers</field><field name="subject">Mice as laboratory animals</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phb5644.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24719944</field></doc><doc><field name="title">A historical perspective on recent landscape transformation: integrating palaeoecological, documentary and contemporary evidence for former vegetation patterns and dynamics in the Fleurieu Peninsula, South Australia</field><field name="creator">Bickford, Sophia Anastasia.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (p. 301-319). Palaeoecological records, documented historical records and remnant vegetation were investigated in order to construct a multi-scaled history of vegetation pattern and change in the Fleurieu Peninsula, South Australia over the last c. 8000 years. Aims to better understand post-European landscape transformation and address the inherently historical components of the problems of regional biodiversity loss, land sustainability and the cumulative contribution to global climatic change.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Fragmented landscapes South Australia Fleurieu Peninsula</field><field name="subject">Remnant vegetation South Australia Fleurieu Peninsula</field><field name="subject">Vegetation management South Australia Fleurieu Peninsula</field><field name="subject">Landscape ecology South Australia Fleurieu Peninsula</field><field name="subject">Paleobiology South Australia Fleurieu Peninsula</field><field name="subject">Vegetation surveys South Australia Fleurieu Peninsula</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phb583.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24720003</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Investigation of vitamin B&#209;&#210; deficiency in ruminants : a thesis in fulfilment of the requirements for admission to the degree of Doctor of Philosophy of the University of Adelaide</field><field name="creator">Babidge, Wendy.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 202-21). Experiments were designed for the early detection of vitamin B&#209;&#210; deficiency in sheep and cattle. Metabolic indicators were examined in animals where deficiency was induced with either nitrous oxide (N&#210;O) or by feeding diets of low cobalt content. Results showed that vitamin B&#209;&#210; dependent enzymes in the liver of ruminants appeared to be affected only at a late stage of deficiency. However changes in concentrations of metabolites of these pathways occured earlier.</field><field name="date">1993</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phb1146.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24720028</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Production and function of a soluble c-Kit molecule</field><field name="creator">Read, Stuart Hamilton.</field><field name="description">"Research conducted at the Department of Haematology, Hanson Centre for Cancer Research, Institute of Medical and Veterinary Science."--T.p. Includes bibliographical references (leaves 170-214). Elevated levels of receptor tyrosine kinases have been implicated in carcinogenesis. It is possible that high expression of c-Kit by the leukaemic cell provides them with a growth advantage over their normal counterparts in the bone marrow microenvironment. Thus, a means of inhibiting the interaction of c-Kit on these cells with ligand Steel Factor may remove proliferation and survival signals. Main aim of the study was to produce a biological inhibitor  of this interaction and evaluate its ability to prevent ligand Steel Factor from binding to c-Kit on live cells.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Protein-tyrosine kinase</field><field name="subject">Hematopoiesis</field><field name="subject">Receptor-ligand complexes</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phr2845.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24720032</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Separation and preparation of epimeric alcolhols of the cyclohexane series</field><field name="creator">Jackman, L. M. (Lloyd Miles)</field><field name="description">Typewritten copy Undertakes research on epimeric disubstituted cyclohexanes. Describes the results of several methods of preparation and isolation of "cis" and "trans" epimeric alcohols related to cyclohexane</field><field name="date">1949</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Cyclohexane</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09SM/09smj12.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24720104</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Investigation of the physiological basis of the rind disorder oleocellosis in Washington navel orange (Citrus sinensis [L.] Osbeck)</field><field name="creator">Knight, Toby George.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 152-164) Microscopy investigations into the oil glands, localisation of the rind oils and the development of oleocellosis have been carried out in Washington navel orange (Citrus sinensis [L.] Osbeck). Aims to develop an improved understanding of the physiological basis of the rind disorder.</field><field name="date">2002</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Orange Diseases and pests</field><field name="subject">Citrus Diseases and pests</field><field name="subject">Citrus fruits Physiology</field><field name="subject">Citrus fruits Harvesting</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09AHP/09ahpk71.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24720190</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Social exclusion as a policy framework for the regeneration of Australian public housing estates</field><field name="creator">Arthurson, Kathy (Kathryn Diane)</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 288-332) Concerned with the utility of the concept of social exclusion in Australian housing and urban policy. The question is explored through comparative analysis of the inclusionary strategies that comprise Australian housing authorities' "whole of government" approaches to estate regeneration, on six case study estates, two each in New South Wales, South Australia and Queensland.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Marginality, Social Australia</field><field name="subject">Assimilation (Sociology) Australia</field><field name="subject">Housing policy Australia</field><field name="subject">Social structure Australia</field><field name="subject">Public welfare Australia</field><field name="subject">Sociology, Urban Australia</field><field name="subject">Human geography Philosophy</field><field name="subject">Australia Social policy 1990-</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09pha791.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24720295</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The oral health of older adults with dementia</field><field name="creator">Chalmers, Jane.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 347-361. Presents results of 2 longitudinal studies investigating the oral health of older adults with dementia, using questionnaires and clinical inspections at baseline and one year. Groups studied were nursing home residents and those living in the community, with moderate to severe dementia or no dementia diagnosis. Caries experience was related to dementias severity and not to specific dementia diagnoses. Coronal and root caries experience was higher in dementia participants with moderate-severe dementia, the socio-economically disadvantaged, more functionally dependent, taking neuroleptic medications with high anticholinergic adverse effects, with eating and swallowing problems, were not attending the dentist, who needed assistance and were behaviourally difficult during oral hygiene care and whose carers were burdened.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Older people Dental care South Australia Adelaide</field><field name="subject">Dementia Patients Care South Australia Adelaide</field><field name="subject">Dental surveys South Australia Adelaide</field><field name="subject">Dental public health South Australia Adelaide</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phc438.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24720341</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Smoking and periodontal disease in Vietnamese middle-aged population</field><field name="creator">Do, Giang Loc.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references. Electronic publication; full text available in PDF format; abstract in HTML format. The present study aimed to describe the prevalence, extent and severity of chronic adult periodontitis among representative Vietnamese middle-aged adults. Also, it aimed to investigate smoking, which is highly prevalent in Vietnam, as a risk indicator for periodontal disease in a population with minimal access to dental care. Electronic reproduction.[Australia] :Australian Digital Theses Program,2001.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="identifier">http://thesis.library.adelaide.edu.au/adt-SUA/public/adt-SUA20020130.114008</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24720489</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Optical studies of the mesospheric region</field><field name="creator">Woithe, Jonathan Mark.</field><field name="description">Includes copies of articles co-authored by the author during the preparation of this thesis. Includes bibliographical references. Electronic publication; full text available in PDF format; abstract in HTML format. A three-field photometer was employed at the University of Adelaide's Buckland Park field site to collect optical observations of the 557.7nm OI and 730nm OH airglow emissions on an almost continuous basis since May 1995 to May 2000, with observations made whenever the moon was not up. Electronic reproduction.[Australia] :Australian Digital Theses Program,2001.</field><field name="date">2000</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Airglow Observations</field><field name="subject">Gravity waves</field><field name="subject">Mesosphere</field><field name="identifier">http://thesis.library.adelaide.edu.au/public/adt-SUA20021206.142350/index.html</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24720490</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The conduct of travel : beginning a genealogy of the travelling subject</field><field name="creator">Bonham, Jennifer D. (Jennifer Dawn)</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 233-248). Draws on insights of feminist and post-structuralist theorists to question the way in which urban travel is currently reflected upon by urban professionals and the potential effects of these modes of reflection. Argues that in refusing to explicate the counter practices and counter stories of travel, researchers also ignore the potentially disruptive ways of thinking about and intervening in urban travel and urban space. Uses the City of Adelaide in South Australia, as a site through which to examine the way in which the spaces, bodies, and conduct of travel have been objectified and subsequently intervened upon by urban experts.</field><field name="date">2002</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Urban transportation South Australia Adelaide Metropolitan Area Planning</field><field name="subject">Commuters South Australia Adelaide Metropolitan Area</field><field name="subject">Commuting South Australia Adelaide Metropolitan Area</field><field name="subject">Local transit South Australia Adelaide Metropolitan Area</field><field name="subject">Sociology, Urban South Australia Adelaide Metropolitan Area</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phb714.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24720491</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Public housing tenant relocation: residential mobility, satisfaction, and the development of a tenant's spatial decision support system : thesis submitted for the degree of Doctor of Philosophy</field><field name="creator">Baker, Emma.</field><field name="description">HomeLocater CD-ROM included as Appendix 8.3. Includes bibliographical references (leaves 233-250). An examination of residential mobility, and its outcomes focussing on the forced relocation of public housing tenants from The Parks area of metropolitan Adelaide. Investigates the process of public housing relocation and suggests means of improving relocation outcomes for individual tenants and their household. System requirements for accompanying CD-ROM: IBM compatible computer. Other requirements: InstallShield Wizard set-up program ; Winzip. Adobe Acrobat Reader is required to view or print the PDF files.</field><field name="date">2002</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Relocation (Housing) South Australia Adelaide Metropolitan Area</field><field name="subject">Public housing Government policy South Australia AAdelaide Metropolitan Area</field><field name="subject">Urban renewal South Australia Adelaide Metropolitan Area</field><field name="subject">Housing policy South Australia Adelaide Metropolitan Area</field><field name="subject">Sociology, Urban South Australia Adelaide Metropolitan Area</field><field name="subject">Spatial systems South Australia Adelaide Metropolitan Area</field><field name="subject">Decision support systems</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phb1674.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24720597</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Molecular and cellular studies of zoledronic acid : a potent inhibitor of multiple myeloma-induced osteolysis</field><field name="creator">Pan, Beiqing.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 86-103. Investigates the effect of zoledronic acid on myeloma cells and osteoblast-like cells to establish the molecular and cellular mechanisms responsible for the clinical effectiveness of bisphosphonates in the treatment of patients with myelomatosis. Concludes that zoledronic acid inhibits myelomatosis-induced osteolysis thorugh the mechanisms of myeloma cell death and proliferation and maturation of osteoblasts.</field><field name="date">2002</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Diphosphonates Physiological effect</field><field name="subject">Bone cells Metabolism</field><field name="subject">Multiple myeloma Chemotherapy</field><field name="subject">Antineoplastic agents</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09MSM/09msmp187.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24720623</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Control, compulsion and controversy: venereal diseases in Adelaide and Edinburgh 1910-1947</field><field name="creator">Lemar, Susan.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 280-305). Argues that despite the liberal use of social control theory in the literature on the social history of venereal diseases, rationale discourses do not necessarily lead to government intervention. Comparative analysis reveals that culturally similar locations can experience similar impulses and constraints to the development of social policy under differing constitutional arrangements.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Sexually transmitted diseases Law and legislation South Australia Adelaide History 20th century</field><field name="subject">Sexually transmitted diseases Law and legislation Scotland Edinburgh History 20th century</field><field name="subject">Social medicine South Australia Adelaide History 20th century</field><field name="subject">Social medicine Scotland Edinburgh History 20th century</field><field name="subject">Medical policy Social aspects South Australia Adelaide History 20th century</field><field name="subject">Medical policy Social aspects Great Britain History 20th century</field><field name="subject">Public health Social aspects South Australia Adelaide History 20th century</field><field name="subject">Public health Social aspects Scotland Edinburgh History 20th century</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phl548.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24720637</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Ecopolis : towards an integrated theory for the design, development and maintenance of ecological cities</field><field name="creator">Downton, Paul Francis.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (p. 575-607) Pt. A. Ecological cityscapes: theory &amp; practice -- pt. B. Urban ecology Australia &amp;ecopolis: ecocity projects in South Australia -- pt. C. Towards a theoretical synthesis of ecopolis About creating and maintaining 'ecological cities' and the necessary conditions for making ecocities. Sets the creation of human settlement in an ecological context and demonstrates through case study analyses that practical approaches to urbanism can be made within a theory of city-making grounded in principles of direct democracy and cooperative community processes.</field><field name="date">2002</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Urban Ecology Australia</field><field name="subject">Urban ecology Australia</field><field name="subject">City planning Environmental aspects</field><field name="subject">Human ecology</field><field name="subject">Urban ecology South Australia Adelaide Case studies</field><field name="subject">Urban ecology South Australia Whyalla Case studies</field><field name="subject">City planning Environmental aspects South Australia Case studies</field><field name="subject">Housing development South Australia Case studies</field><field name="subject">Nature Effect of human beings on</field><field name="subject">Environmental health</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phd75151.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24720651</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Becoming and unbecoming: abject relations in anorexia</field><field name="creator">Warin, Megan.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves [287]-309). Concerned with a group of people's everyday experiences of anorexia. The fieldwork on which the thesis is based was conducted in multiple sites (Vancouver, Edinburgh, and Adelaide) over 15 months (August 1998-October 1999) and deals with 44 women and 3 men ranging in ages from 14-55. Primarily concerned with the processes that propelled them towards and away from this phenomenon: the desires, connections, disconnections, practice, contested performances and struggles of becoming and unbecoming 'anorexic'.</field><field name="date">2002</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Anorexia nervosa Social aspects Case studies</field><field name="subject">Anorexia nervosa Etiology</field><field name="subject">Eating disorders in women</field><field name="subject">Eating disorders in men</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phw276b.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24720678</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The inner musical workings of Robert Schumann, 1828-1840 : in two volumes</field><field name="creator">Moon, Geoffrey.</field><field name="description">A thesis which examines Schumann's secret musical language and the development of that language into a highly complex system of extra-musical meanings expressed in tones, special motifs, harmonic progressions and keys. This study traces the development of Schumann's procedures by first analysing the songs of 1840 to see which repeated musical devices connected with texts. Once they have been identified, the application of these devices is then examined, retrospectively, in selected works for solo piano. Relying heavily on Schumann's diaries and letters, as well as a detailed analysis of selected works for voice and solo piano, this study shows the extra-musical meaning to be ultimately concerned with Schumann's wish to marry Clara Wieck and her father's unyeilding opposition to the idea.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Schumann, Robert, 1810-1856 Criticism and interpretation</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phm817.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24720679</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Images of the crucifixion in late antiquity : the testimony of engraved gems</field><field name="creator">Harley, Felicity.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 289-313. A study which takes as its focus five gemstones, each engraved with an image of the Crucifixion and previously dated to the Late Antique period. The study undertakes an examination of the gems' iconographic as well as compositional, physical and epigraphic evidence, and demonstrates the way in which critical information regarding the evolution of the Crucifixion image in Late Antiquity has been seriously obstructed in previous studies through the dismissal, misapplication and misinterpretation of the gems. Focusing on iconography, it presents a revised chronology for the gems, suggesting that only three are Late Antique, the fourth being early Byzantine.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Jesus Christ Art</field><field name="subject">Jesus Christ Crucifixion</field><field name="subject">Crucifixion in art</field><field name="subject">Jewelry, Ancient</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phh285.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24720856</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Modelling cooling tower risk for Legionnaires' Disease using Bayesian Networks and Geographic Information Systems</field><field name="creator">Wilmot, Peter Nicholas.</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographical references (leaves 115-120) Establishes a Bayesian Belief Network (BBN) to model uncertainty of aerosols released from cooling towers and Geographic Information Systems (GIS) to create a wind dispersal model and identify potential cooling towers as the source of infection. Demonstrates the use of GIS and BBN in environmental epidemiology and the power of spatial information in the area of health.</field><field name="date">1999</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Legionella pneumophila Environmental aspects Mathematical models</field><field name="subject">Air conditioning Health aspects Australia Mathematical models</field><field name="subject">Legionnaires' disease South Australia Prevention</field><field name="subject">Legionnaires' disease Epidemiology South Australia Mathematical models</field><field name="subject">Legionnaires' Disease Mathematical models</field><field name="subject">Public health Data processing</field><field name="subject">Environmental health Data processing</field><field name="subject">Geographic information systems</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09SIS.M/09sismw744.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24770954</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Flash flooding in an urban environment : causes, effects, potential damages and possible remedies, with particular reference to Keswick Creek in the inner suburbs of Adelaide</field><field name="creator">Wright, Christopher J. (Christopher John)</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves [175-181]</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Floods South Australia Adelaide Region</field><field name="subject">Flood control South Australia Adelaide Region</field><field name="subject">Flood forecasting South Australia Adelaide Region</field><field name="subject">Flood damage prevention South Australia Adelaide Region</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09ENS/09ensw948.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24770992</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Origin of macrophages in rat syringomyelia : an investigative study using rat radiation bone marrow chimeras</field><field name="creator">Lee, Gabriel Y. F. (Gabriel Yin Foo)</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 155-180.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Syringomyelia Immunology</field><field name="subject">Syringomyelia Animal models</field><field name="subject">Macrophages</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09MS/09msl478.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24770993</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Organotin compounds for catalysis</field><field name="creator">Clarke, David John.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves [89-92]</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Organotin compounds</field><field name="subject">Catalysis</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09SM/09smc5974.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24770997</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Investigation on the population variation of Drosera indica L. complex using combined morphological and molecular techniques</field><field name="creator">Susandarini, Ratna.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 131-159. Drosera indica L. is an annual tropical species of carnivorous plant exhibiting a considerable amount of morphological variability, including plant size, flower colour, stamen form, seed size and seed coat ornamentation pattern. This study aims at investigating the pattern of morphological and genetic variability in this species to determine whether there are morphologically distinguishable groups, and whether these groups are genetically distinct.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Sundews</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09SM/09sms964.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24770999</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Noncommutative spin geometry</field><field name="creator">Rennie, Adam Charles.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: p. 155-161.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Noncommutative algebras</field><field name="subject">Noncommutative rings</field><field name="subject">Geometry, Algebraic</field><field name="subject">K-theory</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phr4163.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24771002</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Leptin action on ovulation and leptin receptors across the rat oestrous cycle</field><field name="creator">Duggal, Priya S. (Priya Sunanda)</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves [124-153]</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Leptin Physiological effect</field><field name="subject">Ovulation</field><field name="subject">Leptin receptors</field><field name="subject">Fertility Endocrine aspects,</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phd866.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24771007</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Gene therapy studies of Adenoviral IL-10 transduced Dendritic cells in allotransplantation</field><field name="creator">Coates, Patrick Toby Hewlett.</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 151-186. Studies the capacity of dendritic cells transduced with the immunosuppressive gene construct adenoviral interleukin-10 to inhibit alloimmune responses in both small and large animal transplantation models. There is promising in vitro evidence for gene therapy to modify dendritic cell function, which in small animal models can modify skin graft rejection. In large animals, genetically modified dendritic cells alone were not capable of prolongation of allograft survival, suggesting that these cells may require adjuvant immunosuppressive therapy to be used in future protocols.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phc6525.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24771010</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Gene/environment interactions in human obesity</field><field name="creator">Heilbronn, Leonie Kaye.</field><field name="description">Errata pasted onto back page. Bibliography: leaves 193-228.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Obesity</field><field name="subject">Obesity Prevention</field><field name="subject">Weight loss</field><field name="subject">Medical genetics</field><field name="subject">Genetic screening</field><field name="subject">Genetic polymorphisms</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phh466.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24771011</field></doc><doc><field name="title">A comparison of methane dynamics between wetlands constructed for wastewater treatment and a natural sedgeland in South Australia</field><field name="creator">Muller, Kerri Louise.</field><field name="description">"Figures, tables and the appendices appear in the volume II". Bibliography: leaves 130-152.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Atmospheric methane</field><field name="subject">Methane South Australia</field><field name="subject">Constructed wetlands South Australia</field><field name="subject">Wetlands South Australia</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phm9585.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24771017</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Role of sefD and sefR in the biogenesis of Salmonella enterica serovar Enteritidis SEF14 fimbriae</field><field name="creator">Botten, James Alfons Desmond.</field><field name="description">Corrigenda attached after the bibliography. Bibliography: leaves 166-206.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Salmonella enteritidis Genetics</field><field name="subject">Pili (Microbiology)</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phb7512.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24771023</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Towards cloning Yd2 : a barley resistance gene to barley yellow dwarf virus</field><field name="creator">King, Brendon James.</field><field name="description">Errata attached to inside front cover. Bibliography: leaves [156-188]</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Barley Disease and pest resistance Genetic aspects</field><field name="subject">Barley Genetics</field><field name="subject">Barley yellow dwarf viruses Control</field><field name="subject">Molecular cloning</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phk523.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24771025</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The teaching and learning of probability, with special reference to South Australian schools from 1959-1994</field><field name="creator">Truran, J. M. (John M.)</field><field name="description">Includes bibliographies and index.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Mathematics Study and teaching South Australia</field><field name="subject">Mathematics Outlines, syllabi, etc. South Australia</field><field name="subject">Cognition in children</field><field name="subject">Probabilities Study and teaching</field><field name="subject">Probability learning</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09pht872.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24771031</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The effects of folic acid deficiency and defects in folate metabolism on chromosome damage in vitro</field><field name="creator">Crott, Jimmy.</field><field name="description">Reprints of the author's previously published articles included as an appendix. Bibliography: leaves 165-188. "This thesis describes a series of experiments that aimed to investigate the effects of folic acid deficiency and defects in folate metabolism on chromosome damage rates in human lymphocytes. The accumulation of chromosome damage over time is an important issue because it is thought to contribute to the mechanism of ageing and the aetiology of diseases of age such as cancer and Alzheimer's disease."</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="subject">Folic acid Metabolism</field><field name="subject">Diseases Causes and theories of causation</field><field name="subject">Cancer Age factors</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phc9515.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24771034</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Plant harvesting from a constructed wetland : nutrient removal and plant attributes</field><field name="creator">Bald, Michelle Leanne.</field><field name="description">Accompanying CD-ROM: excel spreadsheet titled "harvesting model". Bibliography: leaves 187-205. "...it was concluded that wetland design and management were crucial to nutrient storage and removal by aquatic plants. Appreciation of plant reponses to environmetal factors such as nutrient addition regime and water depth, was integral to an understanding of the processess which optimise nutrient removal from wetlands via aquatic plants." System requirements for accompanying CD-ROM: IBM compatible computer with Pentium processor or higher and Windows 95, 98 or NT ; 4 MB or RAM. Other software: Microsoft Excel 97 or higher.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">SUA</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phb175.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24771038</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Aboriginal women's autobiographical narratives and the politics of collaboration</field><field name="creator">Jones, Jennifer A. (Jennifer Anne)</field><field name="description">Bibliography: leaves 273-284. This thesis examines the autobiographical texts of the Aboriginal women writers, Oodgeroo, Margaret Tusker and Monica Clare, in light of the 'community of commitment' which supported their publications. It considers how and why the Aboriginal women elicted outside support and how the ideology of the group informed the epistemology of the text.The role of collaborating white editors and professional editors are examined as crucial in influencing the style and content of the finished piece. The original manuscripts are compared against the published editions and the changes implemented by the editor are described. Following Frantz Fanon and Homi Bhaba, the adoption of the white ideological lattice by the Aboriginal author is characterised as the white mask of colonial mimicry. The outcomes of cross-cultural impersonation of the white editor are discussed, with the editorial collaboration viewed as the imposition of stereotyped representations of Aboriginality.</field><field name="date">2001</field><field name="language">EN</field><field name="relation">QU:SSAH</field><field name="subject">Oodgeroo Noonuccal, 1920-1993. Stradbroke dreaming</field><field name="subject">Tucker, Margaret, 1904- If everyone cared</field><field name="subject">Clare, Monica, 1924-1973. Karobran</field><field name="subject">Aboriginal Australians. Women Biography</field><field name="identifier">http://web4.library.adelaide.edu.au/theses/09PH/09phj7761.pdf</field><field name="identifier">NBD:24771143</field></doc></add>