<add><doc><field name="title">Reasoning and learning for intelligent agents /</field><field name="creator">Sioutis, Christos.</field><field name="description">Intelligent Agents that operate in dynamic, real-time domains are required to embody complex but controlled behaviours, some of which may not be easily implementable. This thesis investigates the difficulties presented with implementing Intelligent Agents for such environments and makes contributions in the fields of Agent Reasoning, Agent Learning and Agent-Oriented Design in order to overcome some of these difficulties.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Machine learning.</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78442</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44110</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Frank Lloyd Wright in Australian architectural journals, 1890-1925 /</field><field name="creator">Law, Jade.</field><field name="description">Frank Lloyd Wright (1867 - 1959) is amongst the most famous architects of all time, and is known as the greatest American architect. His personal life was filled with publicized difficulties and scandal, and he was well-known for his flamboyant and charismatic personality, his innovation modern design philosophies, and for the enormous number of realised and unrealised projects (approximately 450 buildings and another 550 unrealized projects) completed during his career which spanned seventy four years.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Wright, Frank Lloyd,</field><field name="subject">Architecture</field><field name="subject">Architecture</field><field name="subject">Architecture</field><field name="subject">Australian periodicals</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78423</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44109</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">A case study of the interaction between identity, power and inclusive practice in a minority-language school /</field><field name="creator">DiGiorgio, Carla Lisa.</field><field name="description">In the last ten years, the inclusion of students with special needs in the regular classroom has become common practice in schools in many Canadian provinces (Bunch et al, 1997; Cummins, 2000). This is due to government legislation and policy (Special Education Implementation Review Committee, 2001; Valentine, 2001). The difference between policy and actual practice can be studied through analysis of implementation at the school level (Taylor et al, 1997; Duemer and Mendez-Morse, 2002). The issues of identity of teachers, principles, other staff, parents and students have been found to impact stakeholders' self-efficacy and decision making regarding inclusion (Cable, 2004; Chenoweth and Stehlik, 2004; Dyches et al, 2004; Avramidas et al, 2002). Power relationships between stakeholders develop in response to a change such as inclusive policy at the school level (Kugelmass, 2001; Pearson, 2000; Hargreaves, 1992; Blase and Anderson, 1995).</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Inclusive education</field><field name="subject">Special education.</field><field name="subject">Language and education.</field><field name="subject">Politics and education</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78367</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44108</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Socio-demographic distribution of health-related fitness of Thai children /</field><field name="creator">Klanarong, Suntara.</field><field name="description">Background: Childhood overweight and obesity has become a serious problem within both developed and developing countries. Recent reviews show alarming international trends of increasing overweight and obesity levels among children in virtually every country studied. Unfortunately, trend data on the health-related size, shape and fitness of Thai children has not been reported.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Children</field><field name="subject">Physical fitness for children</field><field name="subject">Obesity</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78493</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44107</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Australian adults with acquired brain injury :</field><field name="creator">Evans, Ted.</field><field name="description">The purpose of this research was to explore the role of recreation and leisure assessment for Australian adults with acquired brain injuries in their transition from rehabilitation to community recreation and leisure participation. This research set out to discover if common themes existed concerning the role of recreation and leisure assessment which may assist in the provision of recreation and leisure services for Australian adults with acquired brain injuries.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Brain damage</field><field name="subject">Brain damage</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78385</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44106</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Analysis of a common pool resource :</field><field name="creator">Karatna, Patcharasorn.</field><field name="description">A Common Pool Resource (CPR) is a natural or man-made resource system with open or widespread access where the resources are depletable with increased use. CPR examples include forests, pastures, irrigations, rivers, lakes, and fisheries. This research examines a common pool resource in Thailand, i.e. a canal in Nonthaburi Province (NP). The canal, named Klong Om-Klong Bangkok Noi-Klong Bang Kruai, is utilised for agriculture, transportation, commerce, tourism and aesthetics. Currently, urbanisation threatens the canal through changes in land use along the canal. Also, an increasing amount of garbage and water hyacinths in the canal are degrading the quality of the canal environment and waterway transportation. The aims of this thesis were to identify essential factors in the canal system that support the success of collective action in environmental management. This study analyses CPR management in the NP canal system by applying design principles illustrated by long-enduring CPR institutions. These have been identified by Elinor Ostrom (Ostrom, 1990; 1992) and by analysing the situational variables as barriers or resources for collective action.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Canals</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78326</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44105</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The culture and human resource management implications of advanced manufacturing technology innovation : the case of Nigeria and New Zealand</field><field name="creator">Obi, Christian N</field><field name="description">There is no doubt that technological innovation is an important element in today's business environment. The importance of new manufacturing technologies is increasing as the business environment is becoming more complex and competitively intense. The environments in which organisations are competing and operating are also increasingly cross-cultural due to the advent of globalisation. Achieving organisational objectives as a result of technological adoption is made more difficult when organisations set out to undertake innovations more suited to a different national environment. This might have posed a great challenge for organisations that are engaged in technology innovation, especially in developing countries like Nigeria.</field><field name="date">2005</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Manufacturing industries</field><field name="subject">Manufacturing industries</field><field name="subject">Management</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78462</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44104</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Fuzzy logic and GIS in the spatial definition of protection zones on aesthetic grounds : a case study of Adelaide Hills face zone</field><field name="creator">Kishore, Hari Thotapalli.</field><field name="description">There is an increasing pressure on planners to address rapid urbanisation and its impacts on the aesthetic qualities of urban landscape. This is mainly due to the increased sensitivity of the public towards the environment and its greater role, legislatively mandated, in the decision making process. One of the major challenges in land use planning is balancing spatial equity with economic efficiency, where the aspirations and expectations of stakeholders and those of the broader community, in terms of use of the land and its potential, are evaluated and met in a fair manner. The Hills Face Zone (HFZ) of the Adelaide Metropolis in South Australia, currently extending across nine Local Government jurisdictions, is one such example. The HFZ, which provides an important landscape backdrop to the Adelaide Metropolis, has been identified as critically important in the South Australian Planning Strategy and various Development Plans. It is recognised as providing a distinctive visual character to the city and other significant benefits including biodiversity, tourism and recreation.</field><field name="date">2005</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">City planning</field><field name="subject">Landscape assessment.</field><field name="subject">Fuzzy logic.</field><field name="subject">Geographic information systems.</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78435</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44103</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Context transfer in mobile wireless networks /</field><field name="creator">Duong, Hoang-Ha.</field><field name="description">The mobility of wireless users has created a number of technological challenges, especially when a Mobile Node (MN) changes the point of attachment to the network. In recent years, a great deal of research effort has been spent on the issue of mobility, and resulted in development of general frameworks as well as specific protocols supporting mobility. These frameworks and protocols are intended to solve the problem of IP routing (i.e. finding an IP path) to the MN. Typically, the access network may also establish and keep service state information (service context) necessary to process and forward packets in a way that suits specific service requirements. Context Transfer has been suggested as an alternative way of restoring the service context at the new access network.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Wireless communication systems.</field><field name="subject">Mobile communication systems.</field><field name="subject">Wireless LANs.</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78361</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44102</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The clinical efficacy &amp; feasibility of using horsechestnut seed extract in the treatment of venous leg ulceration /</field><field name="creator">Leach, Matthew J.</field><field name="description">Venous leg ulceration (VLU) affects roughly 0.6 percent of the western population, with the management of this condition in Australia alone accounting for between AUD$554 and AUD$655 million in health care expenditure every year. Apart from these financial implications, VLU is also associated with a number of adverse psychosocial effects, including depression, anxiety, social isolation, impaired mobility and reduced working capacity. Whilst compression therapy remains the primary treatment of choice for VLU, discomfort, poor compliance and potentially serious complications demand that a more convenient, safer and efficacious treatment of venous ulceration be developed. A herbal extract proposed to advance venous ulcer healing through its venotonic, anti-inflammatory, anti-oedema, anti-enzymatic and anti-exudative properties is Horsechestnut Seed Extract (HCSE).</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Leg</field><field name="subject">Blood-vessels</field><field name="subject">Veins</field><field name="subject">Horse chestnut</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78424</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44101</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">A matter of significance :</field><field name="creator">Oster, Candice.</field><field name="description">The focus of this thesis is the regulation of people with genital herpes within the discursive field of the Sexually Transmitted Infections (STI) Clinic. Genital herpes, a viral infection understood to be transmitted through sexual contact, is prevalent in Australia's sexually active population. While the condition is not life threatening, it presents as a 'problem' for research and practice in that it cannot be cured, is easily transmitted, and its symptoms are recurrent. Current research related to genital herpes is located predominately within medical, public health and psychological perspectives that form particular 'problem spaces' within which the 'problem' of genital herpes and people with the condition is 'rationalized, codified, and theorized' (Rose 1998: 61).</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Herpes genitalis.</field><field name="subject">Sexually transmitted diseases</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78470</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44100</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">A study of route choice behaviour in response to the content of variable message signs in Adelaide /</field><field name="creator">Furusawa, Hirofumi.</field><field name="description">One of the important components of Intelligent Transport Systems (ITS) are the Advanced Traveller Information Systems (ATIS) that provide traffic information to manage traffic flow on existing road networks more efficiently.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Intelligent Vehicle Highway Systems.</field><field name="subject">Traffic congestion.</field><field name="subject">Roads</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78510</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44099</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">A surface force apparatus study of the mercury/water interface with and without self-assembled monolayers /</field><field name="creator">Clasohm, Lucy Y.</field><field name="description">The surface force apparatus (SFA) has been an important technique for making direct force measurements and has contributed enormously to our understanding of colloidal interactions. The conventional SFA has been limited to measuring forces between solid surfaces, until recently when a modified SFA was developed at the Ian Wark Research Institute [1]. A fluid drop (mercury) is introduced into the apparatus which allows a range of deformable surfaces to be studied in the SFA. This project is an extension of this technique. Interactions between a mica sheet and a mercury drop are studied, including the modification of mercury with self-assembled monolayers (SAMs) of thiol surfactants, and the drop deformation due to non-equilibrium adsorption effects and hydrodynamic forces.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Colloids</field><field name="subject">Surface chemistry.</field><field name="subject">Thin films</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78377</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44098</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Intelligent support for doctor-patient partnership in the context of diabetes /</field><field name="creator">Ma, Chunlan.</field><field name="description">Doctor-patient partnership has been advocated for achieving effective diabetes management. Such a partnership requires empowering patients with proper knowledge and skills so they are capable of participating in decision-making, effective communication with health professionals and successful diabetes self-management. Although it is well known that patient education should be tailored and prioritised, little research on Computer-based Patient Education Systems (CPESs) has aimed at customising information that is flexible enough to adapt to firstly, the dynamic nature of patients' ongoing information needs and secondly, changes in their personal health and social circumstances. Moreover, except for indirect support for doctor-patient communication through tailored information, current CPESs do not aid patients in formulating their questions.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Expert systems (Computer science)</field><field name="subject">Diabetics</field><field name="subject">Patient education.</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78430</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44097</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Emerging trends in teacher professional development within a career continuum /</field><field name="creator">Owen, Susanne.</field><field name="description">The expectations of schools are changing and significant problems are being experienced in attracting and retaining teachers in the profession. Teachers are expected to provide programs to enable a wider range of students to complete their schooling in preparation for work and further study, as well as supporting the social and emotional development of these young people. Accountability requirements for improved student learning outcomes in terms of literacy and numeracy are also increasing. While resourcing and class size are issues, teacher quality has been determined as the most significant aspect in student learning, with support for beginning teachers and ongoing professional development being essential to upgrade teacher skills and knowledge throughout their careers. Decentralisation of education through local school management means that profession development opportunities are being provided at the local level and are linked to school improvement.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Teachers</field><field name="subject">Teachers</field><field name="subject">Career development.</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78356</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44096</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Modelling of sulphide minerals :</field><field name="creator">Huang, Guozhi.</field><field name="description">In this study the unique Magotteaux Mill&#174; system was used to control the grinding chemical conditions, which may be adjusted by varying grinding media, purging gas and pH, during grinding. An electrochemical apparatus was used to investigate oxidation-reduction behaviour of grinding media and sulphide mineral electrodes, as well as their galvanic interaction in-situ of the Magotteaux Mill&#174;. Galvanic interaction between the grinding media (mild steel, 15% chromium, 21% chromium and 30% chromium media) and the sulphide minerals (bornite, arsenopyrite and pyrite) was initially quantified in-situ of the mill by electrochemical techniques under different grinding atmospheres (nitrogen, air and oxygen). An innovative mathematical theoretical model was developed to describe the effect of galvanic interaction on oxidation rates of the grinding media during grinding, which was verified by the experimental data. Galvanic interaction enhanced the oxidation of the grinding media and produced more oxidized iron species in the mill discharge. It was observed that oxidized iron species (EDTA extractable iron) was linear with galvanic current between the grinding media and the sulphide minerals, in agreement with the prediction of the theoretical model. The effect of grinding conditions on pulp chemistry, surface properties and floatability was investigated by the measurement of dissolved oxygen (DO), pH, pulp potential (Eh), ethylene diamine-tetra acetic acid (EDTA) extraction, X-ray photoelectron spectroscopy (XPS) and floatation recovery.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Ore-dressing.</field><field name="subject">Sulphide minerals</field><field name="subject">Flotation.</field><field name="subject">Electrolytic corrosion</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78416</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44095</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The meaning of home and the experience of modernity in pre-apartheid South Africa /</field><field name="creator">Connellan, Kathleen Anne.</field><field name="description">'Home' in a country with a notorious history of division becomes both a material and symbolic handle for belonging. The thesis looks at the nature of home making and home building as it is subjected to conflicts of tradition and domestic design organisation. The material objects together with the physical as well as the psychological spaces of home in South Africa exemplify the struggle with the ironies of a nascent modern era.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Design</field><field name="subject">Home</field><field name="subject">Dwellings</field><field name="subject">Material culture.</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78468</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44094</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Design, consumption and the diffusion of technological innovations in LAN gaming culture :</field><field name="creator">Raimondo, Nicholas.</field><field name="description">The use of 'ethnographic research' to solve problems in the relationship between technology and culture has resulted in a simplification of the role of 'design' in product development, especially in the design and diffusion of technological innovations. Norman (1990, 1998, 2004) decries the popular 'focus group' design research method as misleading and inappropriate, preferring instead a model for 'rapid ethnography' which may lead designers to understand product uses within their social environment. In the same vein, the 'product semantics' of Krippendorff and Butter (1984), and the 'high design' approach of various industry professionals, aim to enhance the designer's understanding of the consumer's individual 'needs' and 'desires.'</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Technological innovations</field><field name="subject">Design, Industrial</field><field name="subject">Computer games</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78502</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44093</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">An empirical study of undergraduates' preference for employment in family businesses /</field><field name="creator">Low, Roger Kit Fai.</field><field name="description">Family businesses have fuelled the growth of the Singapore economy since the 1960s. Many large Singapore companies, including a significant number of those listed on the Stock Exchange of Singapore, are family-owned and controlled. When a family business grows, it requires the services of well-educated and qualified professionals. Consequently, family businesses need to attract and retain these professionals. However, little is known about the preference for family businesses as work organisations among professionals. This study examined business undergraduates' perception of work life in family businesses and their preference for such work organisations after graduation.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Family-owned business enterprises</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78384</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44092</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Effects of language on brand names :</field><field name="creator">Hsu, Nancy Y. M.</field><field name="description">This research project is a study of the phenemenon of foreign branding and the extent of brand name localistion for brands conducting business in Hong Kong. It aims at exploring the effects of language on brand names for the purpose of supporting brand marketing.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Brand name products</field><field name="subject">Brand name products</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78334</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44091</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Preparing academics to integrate learning technologies into their teaching in higher education /</field><field name="creator">Hodgson, Paula.</field><field name="description">The application of an electronic mode of learning (e-learning) has become increasingly important in education in Hong Kong. This study has explored the training and support available for academics who were prepared to integrate learnig technologies into university teaching.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Computer-assisted instruction</field><field name="subject">Educational technology</field><field name="subject">Education, Higher</field><field name="subject">Information technology</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78463</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44090</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The causes and level of distribution channel conflict of China telecommunication industry /</field><field name="creator">Lu, Jinghai.</field><field name="description">The differences between Chinese distribution channels and western distribition channels are neglected. This study, which was conducted empirically in China, with the method of survey, investigates the conflict causes in channel of China TI. The results indicate that there are four causes of channel conflict.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Telecommunication</field><field name="subject">Telecommunication equipment industry</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78454</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44089</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">On urban water pricing with practical application of fuzzy logic model and analytic hierarchy process in Shanghai /</field><field name="creator">Weide, Mao.</field><field name="description">Thesis (DBA(DBusinessAdministration))--University of South Australia, 2005.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">Text in Chinese.</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Water-supply</field><field name="subject">Water-supply</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78341</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44088</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Study of fast cost estimation system for building projects in China</field><field name="creator">Wang, Lianyun</field><field name="description">In the field of construction engineering, effective management of projects relies on domain knowledge and experience. However, many domain problems cause difficulty on performing projects in China. Such problems include difference between planned and market economies, difference between fixed-price and bill of quantity estimations, lack of domain experts for foreign investor, and so forth.</field><field name="date">2005</field><field name="language">Text in Chinese.</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Building</field><field name="subject">Building</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78478</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44087</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Managing intangible returns from customer relationship management projects in the financial services industry /</field><field name="creator">Bellhouse, Michael</field><field name="description">This research portfolio consists of three papers that together investigate the intangible returns generated from customer relationship management (CRM) programmes.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Financial services industry.</field><field name="subject">Financial institutions.</field><field name="subject">Customer relations</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78399</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44086</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Measuring student perception of service quality in higher education :</field><field name="creator">Hoe, Teh Chin.</field><field name="description">The deployment of service quality as a source of competitive advantage is becoming increasingly important to higher education institutions as the higher education market becomes globalised and competitive pressure intensifies. To some institutions, the focus on service quality is a necessity due to governmental requirements and the need to be more accountable to the public. To others, the interest in service quality takes on a more pro-active stance since there are many advantages associated with it: student satisfaction and retention, positive word-of -mouth recommendations, higher market share, and improved financial performance.</field><field name="date">2004</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Education, Higher</field><field name="subject">Universities and colleges</field><field name="subject">Quality assurance.</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78349</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44085</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Problems and prospects of Taiwan's chain stores industrial in growth and globallization /</field><field name="creator">Hua, Chang Sheng.</field><field name="description">Chain store business through different operations (such as franchise system) has developed quickly around the world. Especially in mainland China and Taiwan, chain stores have been growing dramatically. This research discusses the internal and external problems from chain businesses to become internationalization and globalization based in their franchise system.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">Text in English and Chinese.</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Chain stores</field><field name="subject">Franchises (Retail trade)</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78443</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44084</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The relationship of technology transfer and absorptive capacity an empirical study for Taiwan and China /</field><field name="creator">Wang, Eade.</field><field name="description">Technology transfer (IT) is a concept embodied with many complex factors. This study focuses on Research and Development (R&amp;D) Absorptive Capacity (AC) of both ends of the partnership during IT.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Technology transfer</field><field name="subject">Technology transfer</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78449</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44083</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Managing the family's wealth in unstable times :</field><field name="creator">Goekmen, Ariel Sergio.</field><field name="description">Unstable times have been with mankind since recorded history began, markedly so since September 11th 2001, and its effects on the financial markets have led to substantial loss of wealth, especially for wealthy families. The wealth of these families is widespread: it often contains a family business at its heart, and includes property and portfolio assets as well as art collections and other important assets, often spread over many jurisdictions. Advisors can help or hinder the wealth preservation efforts of wealthy families.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Wealth.</field><field name="subject">Family-owned business enterprises</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78350</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44082</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Corporate governance, ownership structure and firm performance :</field><field name="creator">Preedanan, Narong.</field><field name="description">This study examines the relationship between ownership structures and the performance of listed Thai financial firms, using a sample of 39 companies which is accounted for 86% of the market capitalisation of all financial firms listed on the Stock Exchange of Thailand (SET) in 1996. The study employs both univariate and multivariate regression analysis. The empirical results reveal that the presence of controlling shareholders is associated with higher performance, particularly when measured, for example, by return on equity (ROE). This evidence is consistent with the view that large shareholders mitigate the &#8220;free-rider&#8221; problem of monitoring a management team, and reduce agency costs, as contended by Shleifer and Vishny (1986) and Admati et al. (1994). In addition, the separation of voting and cash-flow rights through the use of pyramid and cross-shareholding is not detrimental to the value of a firm. The study does not find evidence to support the argument that a family's involvement in management has a negative effect on company performance. Rather, there is strong evidence to support the hypotheses that state-owned financial institutions display superior performance. Finally, the study does not find evidence to support the argument that there is a non-monotonic relationship between ownership concentration and company value. Nevertheless, there is strong evidence that, at higher levels of ownership (in this case 50-75%), the involvement in management by controlling shareholders has a positive effect on firm performance, in terms of accounting, ROE, and market measures, price-to-book ratio. The results add to the literature that evaluates an empirical the link between ownership structure and firm performance, and provide additional information to policy-makers engaged in the ongoing development of corporate governance in developing countries, particularly in Thailand.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Corporate governance</field><field name="subject">Business enterprises</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78392</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44081</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Customer preferences and choice behaviours towards economy hotels :</field><field name="creator">Shen, Gang.</field><field name="description">Consumers (travellers) choice behaviours and preferences towards different kinds of hotels are of critical importance in tourism and hospitality management. Only by better understanding consumer behaviours and choices can managers design products and services more valuable and attractive. Although considerable research has been done on consumer behaviours, little is known about travellers choice behaviours towards different kinds of hotels (no-star/star hotels) in the Chinese context. Due to the intensified competition and vigorous growth of foreign luxury hotels in Shanghai, the managers of economy hotels (non-star hotels, or motels) badly need marketing strategies to strengthen their competitive advantages and safeguard their essential market share. With the booming of tourism in China, economy hotels will play an increasingly key role in competitive market.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">Text in Chinese ; Abstract and bibliography in English.</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Hotel management</field><field name="subject">Consumer behavior</field><field name="subject">Hotels</field><field name="subject">Tourism</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78494</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44080</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">A study on urban infrastructure project classification model :</field><field name="creator">Sun, Jian Ping.</field><field name="description">The rapid development of economy and society in Shanghai has dramatically spurred the demand of improving city infrastructure. Great concerns have been given to the problems existing in the financing and construction of infrastructure, such as lacking construction funds, low efficiency of construction funds usage, and high financing cost.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">Text in Chinese.</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">City planning</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78433</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44079</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The determinants of the pricing of initial public offerings --- :</field><field name="creator">Hsu, Shou Ming.</field><field name="description">The aim of this research is to identify and compare the determinants for the pricing phenomenon of initial public offerings (IPOs) in the Hong Kong Stock Exchange (HKSE) and Taiwan Stock Exchange (TSE). By comparing and contrasting the similarities and dissimilarities of the determinants, the differences of each exchange can be revealed and offer an opportunity for businesses to explore for their advantages.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Stock exchanges</field><field name="subject">Stock exchanges</field><field name="subject">Stocks</field><field name="subject">Stocks</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78359</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44078</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">A critical evaluation of Taiwan's biotechnology industry /</field><field name="creator">Liu, Brian Chiahao.</field><field name="description">Biotechnology is one of the most important emerging technologies of the 21st century and has already attracted worldwide interest. Biotechnology has been touted as the next revolution in the high technology industry following the computer-telecommunications boom. Modern biotechnology is now widely applied to almost all areas of human life, such as medicine, pharmaceuticals, agriculture, food products, energy, and environmental ecology. However, biotechnology can be said to be still in its early developmental stage and both developed and developing countries recognize its potential contribution.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Biotechnology industries</field><field name="subject">Biotechnology</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78501</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44077</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Financing of infrastructure projects in Taiwan /</field><field name="creator">Cheng, Chung-Lin.</field><field name="description">Taiwan has recently implemented laws, regulations, and institutions aimed at facilitating private sector participation in public works and government procurement to attract foreign expertise and private capital and bring its regulatory framework into line with WTO commitments. Private sector participation involves balancing the interests of government, lenders, private entity and the general public and requires an enabling environment to be successful.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Infrastructure (Economics)</field><field name="subject">Infrastructure (Economics)</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78376</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44076</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Improving the performance of two dimensional facial recognition systems :</field><field name="creator">McLindin, Brett Alan.</field><field name="description">In recent times, there has been an increase in national security awareness with a focus on improving current practices relating to the identification and verification of individuals and the reduction of identity fraud. One tool that has been found to assist in these areas is biometrics. This thesis examines some biometric technologies that may be potentially suitable for surveillance and access control applications, and shows why facial recognition technology has been the focus of this study.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Human face recognition (Computer science)</field><field name="subject">Biometry</field><field name="subject">Computer vision.</field><field name="subject">Image processing.</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78332</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44075</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Developing internationalism in the internationalised university :</field><field name="creator">Bretag, Tracey.</field><field name="description">This portfolio comprises three research projects undertaken between 2001 and 2004, and is a response to both the broad and local contexts of my work as an English as a second language (ESL) educator in a business faculty at an Australian university. Based in my own experience, and foregrounded by my perspectives on education generally and international education specifically, I have used an overarching practitioner research approach. The contextual literature underpinning the three inter-related projects is provided by globalisation and neoliberalism, the changed landscape of higher education in Australia, the internationalisation of higher education, teaching English as a second language (TESOL), English as an international language (EIL), Australian academic standards and intercultural communication.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Students, Foreign</field><field name="subject">Education, Higher</field><field name="subject">Internationalism.</field><field name="subject">International education.</field><field name="subject">English language</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78455</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44074</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The woman who was (not) there :</field><field name="creator">Furler, Loene.</field><field name="description">The purpose of the thesis is to reflect upon the female nude imagery in the counterculture publication London Oz 1967 - 1968, with the retrospective understanding that the alienation involved had a profoundly detrimental effect on my art practice at the time. My aim is to interrogate the past with a view to informing creatively my present work. My thesis is a body of paintings accompanied by an exegesis and a catalogue, from the shed to the dining room and back, 2002, as a work in progress of the MVA.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">London Oz.</field><field name="subject">Underground press</field><field name="subject">Female nude in art.</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78429</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44073</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Seismic retrofitting techniques for existing unreinforced masonry structures /</field><field name="creator">Chuang, Shih-Wei.</field><field name="description">In the last decade, Australian civil engineers have not paid enough attention to earthquake resistant design of structures. It was commonly believed that the earthquake risk was insignificant thus earthquake resistant design was not considered for most buildings. Earthquake resistant design of structures has become an important issue in Australia following the Newcastle earthquake in 1989.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Earthquake resistant design.</field><field name="subject">Buildings</field><field name="subject">Buildings</field><field name="subject">Masonry</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78369</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44072</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The vision-learning debate :</field><field name="creator">Paech, Merri.</field><field name="description">International debate exists between several disciplines about when and how young people's vision should be screened and the relationship between vision and learning. This thesis is concerned with whether adolescents' acuity and binocular functioning can be accurately screened by a registered nurse (RN) and the impact of such a Primary Health Care (PHC) initiative on the participants. The aims of this study include to: screen the monocular and binocular vision of students aged 12 - 13 years; determine the accuracy and efficacy of the screening process; gain insight into the impact of undetected visual problems on the students' experiences with schoolwork and leisure activities; determine why young people are compliant or non-compliant with optometric intervention; and to gain insight into the impact of optometric interventions.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Vision disorders in children.</field><field name="subject">Vision</field><field name="subject">Visual learning.</field><field name="subject">Opthalmic nursing.</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/78415</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44071</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Early adolescent students engage with biblical text:</field><field name="creator">Greaves, Stephen John</field><field name="description">Early adolescent students from Australian Catholic schools demonstrate a variety of implicit understandings and make meaning in a range of ways when asked to engage a biblical text involving Jesus and His interaction with a man possessed by an unclean spirit (Mark 1:21-28). Students in twenty first century Western culture make meaning from ancient texts in ways that reflect the characteristics of their specific age group, their participation in Catholic schools activities and their immersion in the wider popular culture.</field><field name="date">2005</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Catholic Church</field><field name="subject">Bible.</field><field name="subject">Christian education of children</field><field name="subject">Religion</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81693</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44070</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The development and evaluation of a 'clean and green' decision-support system for sustainable competitive advantage :</field><field name="creator">Wong, Hung Kun Ken.</field><field name="description">The aim of this thesis was to develop and evaluate a Clean and Green Decision-Support System by exploring the practice of a large Australian Winery and developing a decision-support system that would facilitate movement towards clean and green wine product packaging. This thesis took into account the relationship between wine manufacturers and their packaging suppliers as shared information between these parties is central to the National Packaging Covenant (NPC) which is an outcome of concern for the environment. This concern has had a dramatic impact upon this relationship in the wine industry because each has to comply with Government regulations and customer demand for environmentally friendly packaging.</field><field name="date">2005</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Wine industry</field><field name="subject">Wine bottles</field><field name="subject">Packaging</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81686</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44069</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The qualities of successful chief executive officers :</field><field name="creator">Wood, John.</field><field name="description">Leadership research has generally overlooked the qualities of successful CEOs, instead focusing on other levels of management. This study sought to identify the personal qualities that made CEOs successful. A literature review identified that there were five qualities associated with success including philosophies about life, self and others, characteristics, leadership style, areas for improvement and lessons taken from experience. A Model of CEO Success is proposed based on these qualities and the relationship between them.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Leadership</field><field name="subject">Chief executive officers.</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81765</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44068</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The approaches taken by Hong Kong senior managers in evaluating the performance of workers /</field><field name="creator">Lee, Jenny Shu Yee.</field><field name="description">The prevailing conceptualization of employee performance is that performance is due to both innate and acquired characteristics of the employee. While the innate characteristics (such as personality or intelligence) are viewed as outside the manager's ability to control, the acquired characteristics (such as skills or behaviours) are subject to managerial control. As a result of this, a great deal of emphasis in Western theories has been on accurately measuring performance, and on providing appropriate interventions to being about an improvement in performance. In particular, the Western theories have concentrated upon the cognitive models underlying managers' evaluations of subordinate performance, since these cognitive models influence both the evaluations and actions that managers take. Using the knowledge, systems have been developed to help managers improve the accuracy and effectiveness of performance evaluation. Examples of practices adopted include the setting of external performance standard through job analysis, the development of rating methods to guide the evaluation process, and the provision of feedback.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Performance measurement.</field><field name="subject">Management</field><field name="subject">Employees</field><field name="subject">Personnel management</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81635</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44067</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Collaborative agent learning using knowledge based intelligent techniques /</field><field name="creator">Farooque, Saulat.</field><field name="description">The area of Agent Technology is a relatively new area and one that has generated great interest within computing circles. The concept of software identities that have the intelligence to perform some of the tasks that humans perform has great potential. Such software identities are slowly making their way into many complex systems ranging from air traffic control systems to web search engines, and removing the direct need for the 'human in the loop'. This type of software that has the ability or intelligence to perform some of the tasks that would otherwise be performed by humans has been coined the term 'Intelligent Agents'.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Intelligent agents (Computer software)</field><field name="subject">Neural networks (Computer science)</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81743</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44066</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The efficacy of an isokinetic muscle conditioning program in acquired brain injury /</field><field name="creator">Killington, Maggie.</field><field name="description">The purpose of this research was to investigate the efficacy of a 12 week isokinetic conditioning progam for the lower limbs in 12 young adults with acquired brain injury. There is strong evidence that young adults following ABI (Acquired Brain Injury) have on-going issues with physical impairments and functional limitations many years after their brain injury, and that these limitations are substantial and restrictive. As most therapy resources are available for early rehabilitation only, and these resources are mainly located in large cities, there are many people who are not receiving rehabilitation to support their on-going progress.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Brain damage</field><field name="subject">Brain</field><field name="subject">Muscle strength.</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81789</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44065</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Dynamic territoriality for multi-robot systems /</field><field name="creator">Richer, Toby.</field><field name="description">This thesis proposes a new method of dividing a task between members of a robot team. This method is dynamic territoriality. Territoriality is an emergent method of distributing resources between animals- each animal independently marks and defends their own area. Territoriality has previously been used on robot teams with varying results; these robot territorial systems did little or no adaptation to the environment or task, unlike natural territorial systems.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Robots</field><field name="subject">Territoriality (Zoology)</field><field name="subject">Ants</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81677</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44064</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Health service quality in Australian private sector physiotherapy and chiropratics :</field><field name="creator">Kumar, Saravana</field><field name="description">The decreasing Australian health dollar requires closer scrutiny on what outcome is purchased for it. Quality outcomes are produced by quality services, it is important to identify the constructs of quality care from individual stakeholders' perspectives. Empirical research on quality constructs is limited to medical and nursing literature. Within Physiotherapy and Chiropractics, little research has been undertaken to examine the constructs of quality care from individual stakeholder perspectives, or to develop monitoring systems that reflect the nature and philosophy of Physiotherapy and Chiropractic care</field><field name="date">2005</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Physical therapy</field><field name="subject">Chiropractic</field><field name="subject">Medical care</field><field name="subject">Quality assurance</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81678</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44063</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Using mass idea brainstorming as an organizational approach to jumpstarting innovation initiative /</field><field name="creator">Butterworth, Michael Simon John.</field><field name="description">In 2001, Gerald Haman stormed the corporate world by generating 454 000 ideas in 60 minutes delivering "Thinkathon", which he defined as the &#8220;world's greatest brainstorming tool&#8221;. Easily replicated, Singapore corporate leaders saw the &#8220;Thinkathon&#8221; as a 'quick fix' to jumpstart mass ideas for Innovative Initiatives in the perennial search for that critical sustaining differentiator for the city state to compete regionally and ever more now, as a developed nation, globally. However, the &#8220;Thinkathon&#8221; merely provided a good harvest of ideas, but saw no gains in innovative breakthroughs. Alex Osborn (1953), the father of brainstorming, initiated brainstorming as a 3 phase program of fact-finding, idea finding and solution finding but &#8220;Thinkathon&#8221; provided only mass idea-finding. This thesis sets out to address the gaps in salvaging the effectiveness of mass brainstorming &#8220;Thinkathon&#8221; if organizations in Singapore still opt to engage this &#8220;perceived creative tool&#8221; as a jumpstart for Innovative Initiatives.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Brainstorming.</field><field name="subject">Thought and thinking.</field><field name="subject">Organizational change</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81773</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44062</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Wheelchair prescription in spinal cord injury:</field><field name="creator">Di Marco, Allie.</field><field name="description">Wheelchair prescription is a highly complex clinical practice. Evidence exists that long term success of wheelchair prescription is not always achieved and that rehabilitation professionals are experiencing increasing pressure to demonstrate accountability and cost containment in this area of service delivery. Occupational therapists within a spinal injury unit in South Australia conducted a quality activity to evaluate their wheelchair prescription practice. The quality activity involved consecutive sampling techniques to collect data on 128 wheelchair users who had a wheelchair prescribed between November 1993 and January 1996.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Wheelchairs</field><field name="subject">Spinal cord</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81717</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44061</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Competitive strategies development for marine electrical swichboard industry in China, Singapore and United Arab Emirates /</field><field name="creator">Ong, Pock Keong.</field><field name="description">In today's hypercompetitive and fast changing business environment, companies are increasingly under pressure to find new ways to make their business operations lean and profitable through acquiring a sustainable competitive advantage. Some essential ways of doing this are by looking for improvements in innovative ways and being more responsive to market changes.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Electricity.</field><field name="subject">Competition</field><field name="subject">Marine engineering.</field><field name="subject">Competition</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81642</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44060</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Liposomes in drug delivery :</field><field name="creator">Er, Yan.</field><field name="description">Liposomes are used as biocompatible carriers of drugs, peptides, proteins, plasmic DNA, antisense oligonucleotides or ribozymes, for pharmaceutical, cosmetic, and biochemical purposes. They are considered as effective drug delivery systems due to their colloidal size, easily controllable surface and membrane properties, large carrying capacity of drugs and biocompatibility.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Liposomes</field><field name="subject">Drug delivery systems.</field><field name="subject">Fourier analysis.</field><field name="subject">Adsorption.</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81732</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44059</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">An examination of social systems of engineering projects /</field><field name="creator">Lawson, Errol C.</field><field name="description">The impetus for the research reported in this thesis came after reflection on my career in engineering which led to the observation that descriptions of what engineers do, or should do, when they work on projects, do not address the social aspects of their interactions with other people, both engineers and non-engineers, who are involved with the project. Teams of engineers can be viewed as social systems and I believed that it should be possible to describe their activities using social theories, as distinct from descriptions which focus on the application of technology and the management of resources to meet clients' requirements. The research followed a heuristic methodology. There was no initial theory. Theory emerged from the data. As a preliminary step, I examined documents prescribing the way engineering work is done and compared them with accounts of successful projects. The comparison shows that the prescriptive documentation overlooks the interaction between people, which however features prominently in the accounts of successful projects. As well, examination of the systems representation widely employed throughout projects shows that it can lead to oversimplification, when it is used to model socio-technical and social systems.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Social systems.</field><field name="subject">Engineers.</field><field name="subject">Project management.</field><field name="subject">Leadership.</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81643</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44058</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Administrative staff experiences in the corporate university /</field><field name="creator">Szekeres, Judy.</field><field name="description">This portfolio concentrates on the experiences of administrative staff in universities. The aim of the portfolio is to examine the work and work experiences of administrative staff in the three universities in South Australia, particularly in the light of increased corporatisation of universities over the last fifteen years. Administrative staff are rarely discussed in the literature focused on universities as organisations and workplaces and yet they constitute over half the staff in Australian universities. They are growing in visibility and importance as universities become more corporate in their operation and structure. New occupations have come into existence as a result of the commercialisation of higher education and the accompanying increased government surveillance has resulted in greater professionalisation of administration and administrative work roles. This research brings these changes to the working lives of administrative staff in universities into focus and places their stories at its centre.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Universities and colleges</field><field name="subject">College environment.</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81781</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44057</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Antenna directivity optimization using genetic algorithms /</field><field name="creator">Udina, Andrew.</field><field name="description">One of the fundamental properties of an antenna is its ability to radiate or receive more energy in one given direction over all the others. This property is called the directivity. The optimization of the directivity usually requires a great deal of attention when an antenna is being designed. There are a number of iterative analytical and experimental procedures available for the optimization of the directivity, however they can be manually intensive, and very time consuming when computer simulation is employed.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Antennas (Electronics)</field><field name="subject">Antennas, Dipole.</field><field name="subject">Genetic algorithms.</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81669</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44056</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Connection handover in LEO satellite ATM networks /</field><field name="creator">Grosser, Paul Matthew.</field><field name="description">Satellite-based communications networks can provide personal communications services to markets that are unable to be serviced by terrestrial wireless networks, such as maritime, aviation, military, developing countries and remote industry. Traditional Geostationary Earth Orbit (GEO) satellite communications suffer from high transmit power requirements and long delays. In comparison, Low Earth Orbit (LEO) satellite communications do not suffer these problems, and therefore promise to provide high-quality communications services to small handheld terminals. The convergence of traditional voice, data, fixed, and mobile communications networks, has prompted the extension of common terrestrial networking protocols into terrestrial wireless and satellite networks. The research presented in this thesis focuses on the Asynchronous Transfer Mode (ATM) extensions required to support the frequent satellite handovers that occur in LEO satellite networks.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Artificial satellites in telecommunication.</field><field name="subject">Wireless communication systems</field><field name="subject">Wireless communication systems</field><field name="subject">Asynchronous transfer mode.</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81629</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44055</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Tractive performance of integrated steering-drive systems /</field><field name="creator">Besselink, Bernard Christian.</field><field name="description">This research studied the tractive performance of integrated steering-drive systems by investigating a two-wheel drive vehicle having two independent rear drive wheels and non-driven steerable front wheels. The feasibility of integrating the steering and drive systems and the performance advantages that may be obtained was investigated. In order to demonstrate the feasibility of the concept, the steering system and the drive system of a test vehicle were integrated using a computer with a specially-developed program. The software algorithm developed for the program used the mathematical relationship between the rear drive wheel speeds and the steer angles of the non-driven front wheels to set the steer angles.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Automobiles</field><field name="subject">Automobiles</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81737</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44054</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">An exploratory study of Singaporean Chinese workers' attitude towards the adoption of retirement planning /</field><field name="creator">Or, Kum Hoong.</field><field name="description">Can average Singaporean workers be financially independent on reaching retirement age and more importantly, during their retirement period? Or will they be dependent on social welfare? This major question continues to confront workers, consumers, economists and the Government. The Singapore population is rapidly ageing with impending crisis that confronts the baby boomers with issues of inadequacy in retirement provisions apart from the basic defined contributions of the Central Provident Fund (CPF), rising unemployment and market unreliability. Inevitably the responsibility for adequate retirement preparation will shift from the Government to the workers.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Retirement</field><field name="subject">Retirement</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81725</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44053</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The contribution of a stroke unit to the outcome of stroke patients and the feasability of setting up a stroke unit /</field><field name="creator">Ko, Kwai Fu.</field><field name="description">Within eastern Asia, stroke is a major cause of death and disability, and the burden of stroke in this region is predicted to increase. The incidence of ischaemic and haemorrhagic stroke in eastern Asia is higher than in Europe and America, and a greater proportion of strokes are due to cerebral haemorrhage, for which the outcome is poor. Anecdotal evidence suggests that Chinese populations are associated with a higher incidence of severe intracranial carotid disease than Caucasian populations. High economic cost is frequent, as there is a great need for medical care in the initial phase after stroke as well as a need for long-term assistance in the late phase. Given these issues, advance in stroke management is strongly desirable.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Cerebrovascular disease</field><field name="subject">Cerebrovascular disease</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81650</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44052</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Grapevines, church steeples, family history... stories of local culture and domestic violence in South Australia wine country :</field><field name="creator">Wendt, Sarah.</field><field name="description">The aim of this research was to explore the impacts that local culture in rural places has on women's experiences, and men's perpetration of domestic violence. The Australian literature on domestic violence is abundant. Feminist explanations have brought the issue to the public agenda, and informed services and responses. Yet, in recent years, such understandings have been criticised for being limiting and failing to recognise significant empirical differences in patterns of violence in society or to allow analysis of other factors that play an important role. Furthermore, despite the richness of domestic violence research, only a few Australian and overseas studies have looked specifically at domestic violence in rural areas. These studies have predominantly identified barriers that keep women trapped in abusive relationships. Some researchers have alluded to rural culture based on conservative, patriarchal belief systems and the pursuit of a rural idyll as being amongst these barriers, and have argued that the effects of patriarchal relationships and structures cannot be ignored. Other researchers have argued that the contexts and cultures of rural communities are changing, that there is not one rural community and culture but many varied rural communities and individual identities, and that these need to be understood and explored. Other than recommendations that rural culture needs to be explored, research has not yet concentrated on how local culture plays itself out in relationships between women and man where domestic violence exists in their lives.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Family violence</field><field name="subject">Rural crimes</field><field name="subject">Human services</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81685</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44051</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Building 'community' :</field><field name="creator">Bosman, Caryl Jane.</field><field name="description">This research draws upon the writings of Michel Foucault and a range of governmentality texts to problematise those planning techniques and practices promulgated in an attempt to produce particular ideals of community. To accomplish this I have focused predominantly on the discourses pertaining to the Golden Grove Development. The histories I re-construct from these discourses demonstrate how ideals of community have been constituted and how they act as technologies of government. The goals of these governmental technologies, I argue, were the normalisation of particular suburban subjectivities, with the intent to maximise economic gains and minimise financial, temporal, spatial and social risks. In the discourses of the Golden Grove Development subjects are positioned as docile and self-disciplined individuals who are active in the government of their own conduct. This governmental practice was in accordance with the goals of the planners and developers of the suburban site. The pre-occupation with the production of ideals of community was one that was legislated by indenture. It was also a theme that the developers harnessed and developed to market and sell the development.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">City planning</field><field name="subject">Housing development</field><field name="subject">Community life</field><field name="subject">Suburban life</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81779</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44050</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Risk management practices of agricultural cooperatives in Thailand /</field><field name="creator">Sukkhee, Korakot.</field><field name="description">This research portfolio focuses on the impact of the risks and the successful risk management in agricultural cooperatives. As a consequence, the main purpose of the study is to set a guideline for managing risks in Thai agricultural cooperatives and develop a sound practice for risk management in the future targeted to increase the profitiability of the cooperatives.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">Some text in Thai.</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Agricultural cooperative credit associations</field><field name="subject">Agricultural industries</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81766</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44049</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Industrial relations in Malaysia :</field><field name="creator">Khuan, Lim Weng.</field><field name="description">Paper1: This article critically reviews the various theoretical perspectives of industrial relations encompassing unitarism, pluralism, Marxism, Fordism, neo/post Fordism and post-modernism and applies them to the unique industrial relations context in Malaysia. It is also discusses various Human Resource (HR) theories focusing on both the 'soft' and 'hard' aspects of HR and its impact on industrial relations practices in the Asia-Pacific region based on empirical evidence. It follows with a critical review of the emerging global patterns/trends on industrial relations, debating whether convergence or divergence of industrial relations systems is more evident or whether patterns of industrial relations are co-related to a country's stage of industrialisation. The article questions whether empirical evidence in union-management relations globally points towards adversarialism or collaboration, or co-operation within an adversarial context to constrained conflict within a co-operative framework. The literature gap suggests that further industrial relations research involving employers and employees should be carried out in Malaysia.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Industrial relations</field><field name="subject">Labor unions</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81700</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44048</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Service-driven market orientation and service qualilty in higher education /</field><field name="creator">Ho, Voon Boo.</field><field name="description">Market orientation, the manifestation of the marketing concept, is central in services marketing. However, the contemporary market orientation models are less service-oriented in nature. An extension of market orientation that incorporates the service concept is deemed necessary so as to be more effective in influencing the service performance of service organizations. Besides, a customer-defined market orientation is needed in order to demonstrate the real and market oriented spirit of the service providers.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Education, Higher</field><field name="subject">Education, Higher</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81751</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44047</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Service quality improvement in the hotel industry</field><field name="creator">Tuntirattanasoontorn, Nida</field><field name="description">Paper I: The overall objectives of this research paper are to analyse previous studies and to review the literature regarding service quality improvement in the hotel industry from various kinds of studies and sources in order to ascertain the following things: service quality and its determinants, service quality model, quality improvement model, the approaches for service quality improvement, the factors affecting service quality improvement, and the critical success factors as well as the barriers to success for service quality improvement. These objectives will lead to a better understanding of the various aspects of service quality improvement in the hotel industry. This is one of three research papers on the topic and can be used as a knowledge base for Research Paper II and Research Paper III.</field><field name="date">2005</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Hotels</field><field name="subject">Hotels</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81620</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44046</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Exploring post-merger integration issues in China : comparative case studies of pharmaceutical companies</field><field name="creator">Chung, Edward M</field><field name="description">The study aims to explore the critical issues facing practitioners in post-merger integration (PMI) involving Western and Chinese pharmaceutical companies and to address the strategic management aspects that should be addressed to ensure merger success and synergy realization. By drawing on specific issues, actions/solutions, and outcomes in the post-merger integration of operational/ functional areas, new understanding on strategic management decisions and actions in pre-deal diligence and post-merger integrating process can be generated to explain merger success or failure. The objective of this research is, therefore, to provide more in-depth and substantive propositions to practitioners in Chinese pharmaceutical mergers and acquisitions to achieve successful post-merger integration.</field><field name="date">2005</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Pharmaceutical industry</field><field name="subject">Consolidation and merger of corporations</field><field name="subject">Consolidation and merger of corporations</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81670</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44045</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">From medicines supplier to patient care practitioner :</field><field name="creator">March, Geoffrey John.</field><field name="description">The Australian health system is undergoing substantial changes in response to consumer demands, rising health costs and consequent shifts in government policies. This thesis explored ways community pharmacists could implement new styles of practice. Results indicate that pharmacists can assist consumers to better manage their medications and reduce harm, but it requires a different practice approach to that currently offered. This research has contributed to the establishment of the nation program, Home Medications Review.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Pharmaceutical services.</field><field name="subject">Pharmacist and patient.</field><field name="subject">Pharmacists.</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81788</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44044</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Market orientation in Shanghai automotive industry :</field><field name="creator">Pan, Xiao Yuan.</field><field name="description">The purpose of the research was to determine the levels and forms of market orientation in Singapore auto industry and the relationship of market orientation and busines performance in a transition economy.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Automobile industry and trade</field><field name="subject">Automobile industry and trade</field><field name="subject">Automobile industry and trade</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81759</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44043</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The linkage between diversification and performance :</field><field name="creator">Fang, Peiji.</field><field name="description">Thesis (DBA(DoctorateofBusinessAdministration))--University of South Australia, 2005.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">Text in Chinese.</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Corporations</field><field name="subject">Corporations</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81701</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44042</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Performance pay and motivation :</field><field name="creator">Chee, Peter Lean Hock.</field><field name="description">The chief purpose of this survey is to explore employee's perception and experience with Performance Pay and how they affect motivation in the workplace.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Incentives in industry.</field><field name="subject">Performance awards.</field><field name="subject">Employee motivation.</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81657</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44041</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Management training and development for small business entrepreneurs</field><field name="creator">Laiseh, Anthony Valentine</field><field name="description">This research focused on the management training and development of small busines entrepreneurs.</field><field name="date">2005</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Entrepreneurship</field><field name="subject">Businesspeople</field><field name="subject">Small business</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81709</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44040</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Perceptions of strategic outsourcing :</field><field name="creator">Krajaysri, Witaya.</field><field name="description">Thesis (DBA(DoctorateofBusinessAdministration))--University of South Australia, 2005.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Business logistics</field><field name="subject">Logistics</field><field name="subject">Corporations</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81797</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44039</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Structural equation modelling of the relationship between performance determinants and performance /</field><field name="creator">Lee, Nagarajah.</field><field name="description">The purpose of this study is to develop a performance management framework for public schools.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">School management and organization.</field><field name="subject">Performance</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81664</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44038</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">An empirical investigation of the acceptance of e-learning of Thai university students /</field><field name="creator">Vanichviroon, Songsak.</field><field name="description">The purpose of this study is to examine the acceptance of e-learning by Thai university students.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Internet in higher education</field><field name="subject">Education, Higher</field><field name="subject">Computer-assisted instruction</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81716</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44037</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Lean production implementation by Japanese companies in Malaysia /</field><field name="creator">Zin, Ramly Mat .</field><field name="description">This portfolio explores lean production implementation and the priority given by companies to adopt lean production technologies and practices.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Manufacturing industries</field><field name="subject">Automobile industry and trade</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81656</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44036</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Factors influencing Internet shopping behaviour /</field><field name="creator">Laohapensang, Orapin.</field><field name="description">Thesis (DBA(DoctorateofBusinessAdministration))--University of South Australia, 2005.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Electronic commerce</field><field name="subject">Consumer behavior</field><field name="subject">Consumers</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81708</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44035</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">The language of aprons :</field><field name="creator">Smith, Avis Carol.</field><field name="description">This thesis addresses a gap in research regarding women's aprons. The research concentrates on aprons used or made from the late nineteenth century to the end of the twentieth century by Anglo-Saxon and Celtic women in South Australia.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Aprons</field><field name="subject">Clothing and dress</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81758</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44034</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Management reform :</field><field name="creator">Yodwisitsak, Kangwan.</field><field name="description">Thailand has enjoyed a solid recovery form the crisis of 1996 and the Thai people have benefited from ready access to subsidized utilities. However, the Thai government signed an agreement with several international agencies that requires it to liberalize the Thai market by 2006. This means that Thai state-owned enterprises (SOEs) in those industries opened up must prepare for intense competition. However, a study of the history and performance of Thai SOEs has demonstrated that there are operational problems that need to be resolved. To achieve this, it is first necessary to identify the factors that will lead to success for SOEs in the telecommunications industry, one of those industries soon to be privatized.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Telecommunication</field><field name="subject">Telecommunication</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81796</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44033</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">An operational test and evaluation infrastructure model for the Royal Australian Air Force /</field><field name="creator">Lett, Brookelyn.</field><field name="description">The over, or under-commitment of forces in a combat environment can result in the unnecessary loss of life, and compromise the ability of committed forces to prevail in their missions. Appropriate commitment requires a clear understanding of the capability of available forces, and a key tool in this determination is operational test and evaluation (OT&amp;E). The role of OT&amp;E in the Australian Defence Organisation (ADO), with emphasis on the Royal Australian Air Force (RAAF) is the subject of investigation in this research.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Systems engineering.</field><field name="subject">Operations research.</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81662</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44032</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Key entrepreneurial skills and their acquisition :</field><field name="creator">Sim, Heng Chye Matthew.</field><field name="description">Entrepreneurship is gaining greater interest around the world and many governments are "interested in the creation of cultures that would promote enterprise and create new ventures" (Kirby, 2004, p.510). According to Kanter (1984, p 354) "because of profound transformations in the economic and social environment it should be a national priority to release and support the skills of men and women who can envision and push innovation." This is the case in Singapore where the Government is attempting to change the attitudes of young people so they seriously consider entrepreneurship as a career choice. Although the Government is making major changes in the country's education system to achieve this, it remains unclear how it should be done. Although there have been many studies of the skills of entrepreneurs (for example, Kemelgor, 1985; Appell, 1984; Kirby and Fan, 1995) and the methods of acquiring them (for example, Knowles, 1972; Gibb, 1987), they are mainly in a western context and may not be applicable to other cultures, for example Chinese entrepreneurs in Singapore. Indeed, there is no known study of the identification of key entrepreneurial skills of successful male Chinese founder entrepreneurs and their preferred methods of acquiring these skills. Therefore, this thesis examines, for the first time, the key skills of successful male Chinese founder entrepreneurs in Singapore, and how they acquired them.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Entrepreneurship</field><field name="subject">Success in business</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81621</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44031</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Critical factors for effective retraining programmes for middle-aged unemployed workers in Hong Kong and Shanghai /</field><field name="creator">Yuk,Tak-fun Alice</field><field name="description">The provision of retraining programmes has been adopted by many countries in addressing the problem of unemployment among middle-aged workers. This review of retraining programmes for the middle-aged unemployed covers documents and research studies on these programmes. Retraining has been and is still the most popular strategy adopted by nation states in tackling the problem of unemployment of the low skilled middle aged. "Who is responsible for financing retraining programmes" has been a hotly debated topic, but as unemployment among the middle aged has become persistent, it is found that governments' responsibility in financing such programmes has been more well-accepted; nevertheless, how to enhance the cost-effectiveness of the programmes remains an issue. The present researcher has identified from the research work three other issues which are considered crucial for the successful implementation of retraining programmes. These are: the implementation approach, the programme delivery model and setting programme objectives. Since most evaluative and research studies on the subject matter have been conducted by the Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development(OECD) and mainly cover European countries, the present researcher will conduct an evalutive study in Hong Kong and Shanghai. This will attain two purposes: first, to evaluate the effectiveness of this retraining programme and second, to identify some critical factors that are crucial for effective retraining programmes.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Age and employment.</field><field name="subject">Occupational retraining</field><field name="subject">Occupational retraining</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81750</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44030</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Practices to improve customer adoption of Internet banking in Thailand</field><field name="creator">Poungklin, Eakachai</field><field name="description">Overall this thesis is concerned with the implementation and development of Internet banking in Thailand. Paper 1 is a literature review. It examines the development of Internet banking, world-wide rationale for the use of Internet banking, Internet banking in Thailand and the driving factors which influence banks to adopt Internet banking. The results of this study are beneficial to understanding why many banks in the world are starting to use Internet banking as a marketing tool for increasing competitive advantage over their rivals.</field><field name="date">2004</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Banks and banking</field><field name="subject">Internet banking</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81740</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44029</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Determinants of organizational creativity /</field><field name="creator">Tan, Beng-Huat.</field><field name="description">In a fast changing world driven by human resourcefulness and non-orthodox competition, the strategic role of workplace creativity needs no substantiation. However, as restricted by the conventional perception that creativity is an activity of the brilliant individual, this discussion of creativity as an organizational experience is a rather new phenomenon. Though Malaysian researchers are no stranger to the field of creativity, especially in the educational setting, they have overlooked organizational creativity so far. This portfolio therefore endeavours to narrow the gap by, firstly, reviewing the related literature and proposing a workable model for organizational creativity; and secondly, investigating empirically some of the selected dimensions of this proposed model.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Creative ability in business.</field><field name="subject">Organizational behavior.</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81628</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44028</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc><doc><field name="title">Studies on the effects of audit time budget on auditors' behaviour /</field><field name="creator">Choi, Raymond.</field><field name="description">The aim of this portfolio is to discuss the issue of time budget pressure imposed on auditors. The focus is on the reasons why it exists and the consequences that it may lead to.</field><field name="date">0000</field><field name="language">eng</field><field name="relation" /><field name="subject">Auditors</field><field name="subject">Auditing</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au:8081/1959.8/81774</field><field name="identifier">http://arrow.unisa.edu.au/vital/access/manager/Repository/unisa:44027</field><field name="validLink">False</field></doc></add>